page_name,likes_at_posting,followers_at_posting,type,likes,comments,shares,post_views,entities_identified,post_sponsored,post_age,page_age,positive_reactions,negative_reactions,emoji_reactions,post_text
GoFundMe,1839689,1942958,photo,9,2,3,16,['PERSON'],0,0,4545,7,0,16,preserve portrait possible service veteran sacrifice jeff
Kickstarter,1589842,1587991,link,1,1,0,2,"['DATE', 'ORG', 'PERSON']",0,0,4839,1,0,2,stone unique mini recyclable truly age playhouse beautiful uniquely popup washable fun age creativity promote exploration heritage
Kickstarter,1589842,1587991,link,4,3,0,6,"['ORDINAL', 'DATE', 'ORG', 'PERSON']",0,0,4839,1,1,6,feedback discussion frank inaugural meeting council challenge advisory report meeting council advisory host inaugural council patrick stefanie tony kickstarters advisory annette jose philip member thomas meeting ivan
GoFundMe,1839047,1942443,video,42,42,19,69681,"['CARDINAL', 'DATE', 'PERSON']",0,1,4545,59,1,102,25yearold aid recovery rush five verify burn police heroic five injure burn praise action nicholas 25yearold 18 age
Kickstarter,1589866,1588006,link,5,2,0,5,[],0,2,4839,0,0,5,jrpg count fully deck integrate tarot occult exit jrpg tarot fully deck jrpg integrate tarot
Indiegogo,582560,602828,video,5,2,0,1297,[],0,2,5303,0,0,5,stream hd projector battery builtin 1080p stream hd projector battery builtin 1080p
Kickstarter,1589901,1588019,link,10,2,1,12,['PRODUCT'],0,2,4839,2,0,12,moment adapter anamorphic aspect add modern lense vintage moment lens anamorphic adapter lens classic anamorphic vintage cost
Indiegogo,582560,602828,video,4,2,1,622,['WORK_OF_ART'],0,2,5303,0,0,4,voyager host 455 star happen fandom trek event star happen trek event
Indiegogo,582560,602828,video,2,3,2,562,['PERSON'],0,3,5303,1,2,5,electric alarm wake clock electric alarm wake clock
Indiegogo,582560,602828,video,4,1,0,386,['ORG'],0,3,5303,0,0,4,possible expensive complicated tired printer wonder printing 3d beginner wonder printing 3d beginner
Indiegogo,582639,602900,link,1,1,0,1,['PRODUCT'],0,5,5303,0,0,1,humidifier cute desk surprising submarine test fun humidifier surprising cute submarine fun humidifier cute desk surprising test fun
Indiegogo,582639,602900,video,14,3,4,4604,['PRODUCT'],0,6,5303,1,0,15,humidifier gadget whenever spray actually cute desk adorable mist humidifier gadget whenever spray actually cute desk mist
Indiegogo,582651,602897,link,3,0,0,3,"['CARDINAL', 'ORG', 'ORDINAL']",0,6,5303,0,0,3,supply notify backpack outdoor musthave outdoor ultimate backpack true highly size color versatile gear
GoFundMe,1838581,1941839,link,141,158,15,185,"['ORG', 'EVENT', 'GPE', 'PERSON']",0,6,4545,44,0,185,league opportunity nt ca baseball stage word league disability san jose player league disability thomas exhibition report player
Indiegogo,582668,602910,video,1,7,0,657,['PRODUCT'],0,7,5303,0,0,1,machine foldable rowing gym compact walkingpad machine foldable rowing compact
Indiegogo,582668,602910,video,3,3,1,534,['CARDINAL'],0,7,5303,0,0,3,touchscreen organize manager household calendar display task digital busy organize household digital calendar
Kickstarter,1590070,1588169,link,7,2,0,9,"['FAC', 'GPE', 'NORP', 'PERSON']",0,7,4839,0,2,9,restaurateur restaurant uk curator african reach expand cuisine culinary pave restaurant african
Indiegogo,582640,602877,video,1,1,1,584,"['DATE', 'ORG', 'PRODUCT']",0,8,5303,1,0,2,audiophile industryfirst youtuber close slide earbud real padmate instagram excited pamu instagramcomindiegogo personal anc unbox ig padmate takeover
Kickstarter,1589930,1588019,link,4,1,0,5,"['CARDINAL', 'PERSON']",0,8,4839,0,1,5,serial pursuit graphic novel comic_strip detective killer return wesley graphic comic_strip novel return wesley
Indiegogo,582640,602877,link,1,1,0,1,"['CARDINAL', 'ORG']",0,8,5303,0,0,1,clock hype unboxing shock test sleep bad shock habit clock alarm hype clock test
Indiegogo,582577,602798,video,1,2,1,654,"['WORK_OF_ART', 'PERSON']",0,9,5303,0,0,1,marvel vision captain classic adam sagas comic_strip jim starlin dynamite jim sagas comic_strip
Kickstarter,1589715,1587803,link,3,1,0,4,"['GPE', 'PERSON']",0,9,4839,0,1,4,prolific archive organize editing animation cult movie associate cover cost hollywood journey hollywood classic songwriter cult singer movie chronicle
Indiegogo,582577,602798,link,1,2,0,2,"['ORG', 'PRODUCT', 'CARDINAL', 'PERSON', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'DATE', 'ORDINAL', 'GPE']",0,9,5303,0,0,1,introduce different anniversary hollywood legendary leader focus moment character reporter comic_strip card property drop crowdfundingcampaign 50th crew jim starlin dynamite center legacy jim 50 revisit starlin comic_strip mark panel retrospective unveil creation indie
Kickstarter,1589715,1587803,link,3,5,1,5,['WORK_OF_ART'],0,10,4839,1,1,5,trial supernatural comic trans actionpacked thriller dark ii queer continue fantasy irreverent supernatural trans comic actionpacked incredible threat
Indiegogo,582577,602798,video,2,2,0,566,['TIME'],0,10,5303,1,0,3,immunity dry therapy lung stone breathe minute relief salt allergy boost clean salt dry breathe therapy
Kickstarter,1589600,1587689,link,6,1,0,6,"['ORG', 'NORP', 'PERSON', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'DATE', 'ORDINAL']",0,10,4839,0,0,6,tv production edition director original japanese lead production production animation 15th anniversary
GoFundMe,1835992,1939171,link,185,301,14,301,"['ORDINAL', 'CARDINAL', 'GPE', 'PERSON']",0,13,4545,69,6,260,responder elderly mow veteran california maintain lawn mow lawn hi needs brother wyatt
Indiegogo,582533,602741,video,5,1,2,569,"['QUANTITY', 'PRODUCT']",0,13,5303,0,0,5,gb deck handheld tb display gaming laptop ssd g steam miss processor gpd console ram instead steam miss deck
Kickstarter,1589543,1587618,link,9,3,1,11,"['CARDINAL', 'PERSON']",0,14,4839,1,1,11,production various illustrator deck tarot comic towards loaf amanda illustrate 78card loaf 78 pin cute card deck enamel tarot loaf different pin zine cute round illustrate card enamel tarot
Indiegogo,582535,602739,link,2,0,0,2,"['ORG', 'PERSON']",0,14,5303,0,0,2,notify kitty bad tom bad kitty comeback bad kitty comic tom
Indiegogo,582535,602739,video,5,1,1,817,['ORG'],0,14,5303,1,0,6,tackle lifes vacuum mess mop spill handsfree tackle mess spill handsfree
Indiegogo,582535,602739,photo,1,0,0,1,"['WORK_OF_ART', 'ORG', 'PERSON']",0,14,5303,0,0,1,marvel vision captain classic notify adam sagas comic_strip jim starlin dynamite
Indiegogo,582535,602739,video,3,1,1,638,"['ORG', 'PRODUCT']",0,14,5303,0,0,3,version fave slide earbud comfy padmate upgrade bass pamu deliver fall anc fall earbud anc comfy
Kickstarter,1589494,1587566,link,5,0,0,5,"['ORG', 'GPE', 'ORDINAL']",0,15,4839,0,0,5,notable wit animation studio 10th anniversary studio wit wit recognition boost studio promote worldwide
Indiegogo,582543,602747,video,4,2,0,733,['PRODUCT'],0,15,5303,0,0,4,tabletop unique interactive content hologram 3d holographic hologram
Indiegogo,582543,602747,video,2,1,0,618,['PRODUCT'],0,15,5303,0,0,2,desk stow wfh desk stow wfh
GoFundMe,1835078,1938363,link,112,213,57,253,"['PERSON', 'DATE', 'FAC', 'GPE', 'LOC']",0,15,4545,70,71,253,faith humanity restore toddler rally illinois shooting internet highland rally kevin park colon shooting july north il aftermath
Indiegogo,582543,602747,video,0,1,1,548,['CARDINAL'],0,15,5303,0,0,0,onetouch pepper kitchen grind truly rain eliminate mill automatic precise onetouch pepper grind mill automatic precise
Kickstarter,1589494,1587566,link,6,1,0,7,"['EVENT', 'CARDINAL', 'NORP', 'PERSON']",0,15,4839,0,1,7,sandy ii printing japanese americans 120000 imprisonment cover war garcia cost incarceration war innocent japanese americans 120000
Indiegogo,582527,602727,link,2,3,0,3,"['CARDINAL', 'ORG']",0,16,5303,0,0,2,altis level training ai guest blog personal athome handy workout trainer connected fitness altis level training ai guest personal athome handy workout trainer
Indiegogo,582527,602727,video,2,1,2,534,['PRODUCT'],0,16,5303,0,0,2,connected altis ai real personal hit form workout trainer fitness connect workout hit athome fitness
GoFundMe,1835133,1938286,link,43,137,29,137,"['ORG', 'EVENT', 'DATE', 'GPE']",0,16,4545,16,3,62,affect highland park safety shooting update continue centralized parade hub july verify fourth trust highland park parade fourth july shoot affect chicago highland park illinois parade shooting fourth july verify
Kickstarter,1589433,1587505,link,5,1,0,5,"['PERSON', 'LAW', 'DATE', 'ORDINAL', 'GPE']",0,16,4839,0,0,5,lgbtq section effect cut produce sarah
Indiegogo,582527,602727,video,0,1,0,439,['PRODUCT'],0,16,5303,1,0,1,personal roaster boom coffee roast boom
Indiegogo,582542,602734,photo,0,0,0,0,"['DATE', 'ORG']",0,17,5303,0,0,0,innovation fundraise remember indie happen innovator shoppingyoure browse really things indie
Kickstarter,1589539,1587589,link,5,8,0,9,"['WORK_OF_ART', 'PERSON']",0,19,4839,3,1,9,international final animate hit rogers final international final animate hit
Indiegogo,582587,602771,video,8,1,1,830,['ORG'],0,19,5303,0,0,8,charging ride allterrain industryfirst
Indiegogo,582587,602771,video,5,1,0,560,['PRODUCT'],0,20,5303,1,0,6,personal roaster boom lover coffee roast boom
GoFundMe,1834188,1937327,video,104,254,52,9721,"['CARDINAL', 'DATE', 'PERSON']",0,20,4545,94,5,203,peters spread surprise homelessness random act
Indiegogo,582601,602784,link,1,1,0,1,"['DATE', 'ORG', 'ORDINAL']",0,20,5303,0,0,1,innovation crowdfunde july 2022 store july 2022
Indiegogo,582601,602784,video,5,2,0,499,"['PRODUCT', 'ORDINAL']",0,20,5303,1,0,6,handheld thin ultralight oled ayaneo gamer test fave handheld thin ultralight oled gamer
Kickstarter,1589563,1587609,link,7,3,0,9,['ORG'],0,20,4839,1,1,9,earbud allow audiophile expensive equipment audio earbud pro awardwinning earbud redefine bluetooth standard
GoFundMe,1834490,1937619,photo,66,88,4,88,"['ORG', 'PERCENT', 'GPE']",0,21,4545,6,1,73,computer pursue 27 career robotic generation allgirls science low motivate engineer currently alabama stem number worker quest
Kickstarter,1589554,1587598,link,1,2,0,5,"['NORP', 'PERSON']",0,21,4839,4,0,5,lgbtq culture italian podcast journalist elisa modern activist una per
Kickstarter,1589554,1587598,link,13,24,0,24,"['WORK_OF_ART', 'DATE', 'ORG', 'PERSON']",0,21,4839,1,4,18,zine august rpg 2023 february unbound quest return quest zine delve august lore torch rpg zine deep
Indiegogo,582642,602820,link,2,4,0,4,"['DATE', 'ORG', 'ORDINAL']",0,22,5303,0,0,2,innovation upcoming crowdfunde july 2022 store july 2022
GoFundMe,1834006,1937125,link,121,202,14,202,"['DATE', 'ORG', 'PERSON']",0,22,4545,51,5,177,decade kevin king nearly employee miss loyal burger kevin organize ford 27 shatter kevin ford 27 original increase
Indiegogo,582642,602820,video,2,1,0,412,"['ORG', 'PERSON']",0,22,5303,0,0,2,brand potential panel engage competition truly succeed vision believe win size pitch judge market step excited sara hasan interested congratulation petition brand winner congratulation pitch competition
Indiegogo,582642,602820,video,9,2,0,780,['PRODUCT'],0,22,5303,0,0,9,ordinary clean shower deep ordinary
Indiegogo,582642,602820,video,0,1,0,513,"['TIME', 'ORG']",0,22,5303,0,0,0,advanced worth minute training gym muscle gym
Kickstarter,1589559,1587609,link,5,1,0,5,"['TIME', 'WORK_OF_ART']",0,22,4839,0,0,5,knight monster comic sometimes beautiful romance knights comic_strip gay mm demon romance colorful monster sexy fun
Indiegogo,582642,602820,video,4,3,3,849,['TIME'],0,23,5303,0,0,4,minute outdoors couch within lounge total comfort inflatable lets outdoors within lounge total comfort minute
Indiegogo,582642,602820,video,1,4,1,714,['ORG'],0,23,5303,0,0,1,fold anywhere ride various standard sleek bicycle fun various fold
Indiegogo,582664,602835,link,2,0,0,3,"['CARDINAL', 'ORG']",0,23,5303,1,0,3,strive sign equality agency women company apply empower protect towards position solidarity action aspect leadership freedom organization reproductive 500 statement choose freedom womens reproductive disturbing wellbeing shock safety threaten event sadness
Indiegogo,582664,602835,video,3,1,3,492,"['TIME', 'ORG']",0,23,5303,0,0,3,electric struggle wearable wake alarm struggle clock
Kickstarter,1589575,1587622,link,6,4,0,6,['ORG'],0,23,4839,0,0,6,jason factory anarchy cheese weird gamess lets cheese factory different custom casual cheese factory weird sometimes
Indiegogo,582664,602835,video,5,3,1,681,"['TIME', 'ORG', 'DATE', 'QUANTITY']",0,24,5303,0,0,5,qa 330 indemand cooking less pizza fave ig dual lover pie perfection stateoftheart oven stone tomorrow party 90 pm meantime wood crowdfunde demo scorpio option est fuel inspiration oven pst ig 330 pm scorpio pizza fave
Indiegogo,582678,602850,video,1,2,1,389,"['CARDINAL', 'ORG']",0,24,5303,0,0,1,60 farm plant veggie microgreen kitchen indoors herb farm microgreen kitchen herb
Indiegogo,582678,602850,video,0,2,0,413,"['PERSON', 'PRODUCT']",0,24,5303,1,0,1,collectible edition comic base epic tv hit limited hardcover dynamite boys omnibus cover collect
Indiegogo,582678,602850,video,1,2,1,736,"['ORG', 'PRODUCT']",0,24,5303,0,0,1,sony ultrawide content shoot lense angle photographer ultrawide content lense angle photographer
Indiegogo,582678,602850,video,1,2,1,376,"['EVENT', 'DATE']",0,24,5303,0,0,1,panel marginalized october exciting board con gaming gamer happen 2022 outdoor workshop tabletop convention bad ttrpgs background tabletop convention october happen 2022 gaming exciting
Indiegogo,582678,602850,link,2,1,0,2,"['WORK_OF_ART', 'CARDINAL', 'ORG', 'ORDINAL']",0,24,5303,0,0,2,classic comic official horror notify throwback volume dark icon dynamite vol omnibus rise grave volume comics classic highly finally anticipate
Kickstarter,1589570,1587615,link,7,2,0,8,"['CARDINAL', 'PERSON']",0,24,4839,1,0,8,hunter journey selfdiscovery comic scifi chronicle fringe comic queer issue hunter manager wrong
Kickstarter,1589718,1587759,link,9,3,2,10,['PRODUCT'],0,26,4839,0,1,10,computer ride seamlessly fit integrate tube computer integrate computer connect integrate generation seamlessly protect fit tube
Kickstarter,1589735,1587780,link,3,3,1,6,"['DATE', 'ORG', 'NORP', 'GPE']",0,27,4839,1,2,6,reveal 90 struggle ireland irish sexuality officer notion cope police lgbtq reveal 90 ireland struggle irish sexuality officer notion cope police
Indiegogo,582741,602891,link,1,5,0,5,"['WORK_OF_ART', 'CARDINAL', 'DATE', 'ORG']",0,28,5303,0,1,2,different sign breakfast pin studio zodiac enamel lgbtq flag happen gay pride unique collection pin zodiac pride collection lgbtq flag sign pin 12 zodiac collection enamel several pride
Indiegogo,582741,602891,video,6,2,1,495,[],0,28,5303,0,0,6,retro magsafe actually bank zendure retro actually bank
Indiegogo,582741,602891,video,1,2,3,613,"['DATE', 'ORG', 'MONEY']",0,28,5303,0,0,1,brand streaming win present pitch finally competition 5k prize brand present 2022 pitch competition
Indiegogo,582741,602891,video,8,1,1,867,['CARDINAL'],0,28,5303,0,0,8,air pump 3in1 outdoor lantern air pump 3in1 outdoor lantern
Indiegogo,582770,602911,video,8,1,0,894,"['TIME', 'NORP']",0,29,5303,0,0,8,oven chance final neapolitan inner ease scorpio pizzaiolo pizza close unlock oven inner pizzaiolo pizza unlock
Kickstarter,1589846,1587889,link,29,14,6,30,"['PERCENT', 'QUANTITY', 'GPE', 'CARDINAL']",0,29,4839,1,0,30,lawnmower detect fully edge automate robotic accuracy handsfree lawn intelligent wire robot mower lawn cable app mow control 75 slope management 5000 obstacle
Indiegogo,582770,602911,video,3,1,3,762,['PRODUCT'],0,29,5303,1,0,4,modular swappable charging versatile battery apart fit station modular swappable battery station
Indiegogo,582770,602911,video,2,0,2,411,"['DATE', 'ORG', 'MONEY', 'PERSON']",0,29,5303,0,0,2,brand panel grand finalist invaluable expert competition marketing labs 23 determine win elevate development consultation sean pitch judge 5000 emily prove tomorrow among craft adam officer kristen prize industry june director chief tomorrow winner tune pitch competition
Indiegogo,582785,602925,video,3,1,0,357,"['DATE', 'PERSON']",0,30,5303,0,0,3,dad wishlist figure add gear chance edit gadget happen icymi fathers ment browse dad gadget gear
Indiegogo,582785,602925,video,3,2,0,435,"['DATE', 'PRODUCT']",0,30,5303,0,0,3,tv personalized altis ai aipowered personal fitness trainer hook workout tv personalized aipowered personal trainer hook workout
Indiegogo,582785,602925,video,1,0,0,216,"['DATE', 'ORG', 'PERSON']",0,30,5303,0,0,1,panel jared challenge instead collision globe chat alone becky mail fireside ceo center collision conference
Indiegogo,582785,602925,photo,4,0,2,4,"['ORG', 'PRODUCT', 'CARDINAL', 'PERSON', 'MONEY']",0,30,5303,0,0,4,finalist cash competition pitch 5000 collaboration winner partner brand finalist competition daniel pitch yo amber john sara hasan yoshida indiegogos
Kickstarter,1589880,1587918,link,6,3,1,8,"['CARDINAL', 'ORG', 'PRODUCT']",0,30,4839,2,0,8,machine combination tool easytouse cutting professional cutter welder builtin machine stick air aluminum pulse limit cutting plasma
Indiegogo,582804,602934,video,2,0,0,502,[],0,31,5303,0,0,2,dad wishlist round figure add gear fathersday edit gadget happen miss icymi fathers ment browse dad gadget gear
Indiegogo,582804,602934,video,4,4,0,688,[],0,31,5303,1,0,5,conquer offroade breeze whether terrain commute commuting offroade breeze whether terrain
Indiegogo,582828,602959,photo,11,3,0,11,"['PERCENT', 'EVENT', 'DATE', 'ORG']",0,32,5303,0,0,11,equality significance juneteenth college deep historical marshall lie please important happen innovative ahead emotional justice crowdfunde reflect equality 17 significance juneteenth close deep thru historical office 19 lie observe solidarity please vendor holiday important colleague sunday fall ahead june emotional partner justice reflect
Indiegogo,582828,602959,video,4,0,0,586,[],0,32,5303,0,0,4,dad rounded wishlist figure add gear fathersday edit gadget happen fathers ment browse dad gadget gear
Indiegogo,582828,602959,link,0,0,0,0,"['CARDINAL', 'DATE']",0,32,5303,0,0,0,dad 8 gadget fathersday add figure gear dad 8 gadget gear dad rounded wishlist figure add gear telescopic projector gaming gadget console
Indiegogo,582828,602959,link,0,0,0,0,['ORG'],0,32,5303,0,0,0,dad connect fathersday reach crowdfundingcampaign strategist invention challenging education directly submit center strategy download matter control engage foster
GoFundMe,1831417,1934477,link,81,127,7,127,"['GPE', 'CARDINAL', 'ORG', 'PERSON']",0,34,4545,28,1,110,puzzle passion 9 double round surgery chemo puzzle surgery yorker battle treatment puzzle hi peace got patient breast
GoFundMe,1832494,1935545,video,66,75,15,8773,"['WORK_OF_ART', 'CARDINAL', 'GPE', 'NORP']",0,35,4545,24,1,91,american violin possibly united commission african states ha possibly united states
Indiegogo,582873,602983,video,6,2,6,1073,"['CARDINAL', 'ORG', 'MONEY']",0,35,5303,0,0,6,brand detail final competition box win pitch judge contestant 5000 excited prize brand excited pitch competition
Indiegogo,582873,602983,video,3,1,1,279,"['DATE', 'ORG', 'PERSON']",0,35,5303,0,0,3,panel jared data location matter collision todd globe jennifer forward anywhere becky mail coleman ceo center collision conference
Kickstarter,1590099,1588121,link,3,3,0,9,['PERSON'],0,35,4839,6,0,9,accessory line anthony apparel plan illustrator drag queen apparel queen drag pride
Indiegogo,582873,602983,photo,0,0,0,0,['ORG'],0,35,5303,0,0,0,smash guide content premium forum site education especially icymi crowdfundingcampaign ready plus interactive successful center introduce plus education center
Indiegogo,582873,602983,video,2,0,0,454,['EVENT'],0,35,5303,0,0,2,dad rounded wishlist figure add gear fathersday edit gadget happen fathers ment browse dad gadget gear
GoFundMe,1831937,1934977,video,54,114,28,138699,"['GPE', 'CARDINAL', 'ORG', 'PERSON']",0,36,4545,32,52,138,severe fall river montana resident national park service flooding slam bridge accord river link five slam length bridge lauren sweep might fall montana
Kickstarter,1590150,1588165,link,4,3,0,8,"['NORP', 'PERSON']",0,36,4839,4,0,8,discover controversial personal popular educational justin collection trans word pride edition comic_strip popular experimental reprint justin
Indiegogo,582942,603041,video,0,0,0,0,['WORK_OF_ART'],0,37,5303,0,0,0,dad rounded wishlist figure add gear telescopic fathersday edit projector gaming gadget happen ment browse console dad gadget gear
Kickstarter,1590310,1588316,link,14,21,3,21,"['CARDINAL', 'ORG', 'PERSON']",0,37,4839,3,1,18,inaugural council advisory member council welcome advisory application lead hi thrill hundred directly successful
Indiegogo,582942,603041,video,4,0,0,4,"['PERCENT', 'ORG', 'GPE', 'PRODUCT']",0,37,5303,0,0,4,italy lifetime sustainably notify jacket denim italy jacket denim raw iconic italy jacket price 57 denim retail
Indiegogo,582942,603041,video,3,1,1,704,['ORG'],0,37,5303,1,0,4,room huge size projector sport tv screen throw ultra philips projection hassle tv screen huge gaming hassle fun
Kickstarter,1590310,1588316,link,11,2,0,11,"['QUANTITY', 'ORG', 'CARDINAL', 'PRODUCT']",0,37,4839,0,0,11,aipowered lab detect speed printer failure print 3d 3d ai lab color printer detection pa acceleration pc 7 color carbon 16 20
Kickstarter,1590480,1588481,link,13,3,1,13,"['LOC', 'DATE', 'MONEY']",0,38,4839,0,0,13,30 supportive apply chance win special europe sustainable prize award innovative june distribute 2000 submit platform distribute 2022 award europes recognize multidisciplinary maker sustainable response award responsible innovative
Indiegogo,583004,603093,video,4,4,1,569,['CARDINAL'],0,38,5303,0,0,4,wish wish
Kickstarter,1590480,1588481,link,18,1,1,18,"['CARDINAL', 'ORG', 'PRODUCT']",0,38,4839,0,0,18,switch module builtin board combination cluster mini allow raspberry pi computer cluster pi raspberry app pi module
Indiegogo,583041,603094,link,3,0,0,3,"['WORK_OF_ART', 'EVENT', 'DATE', 'ORG']",0,41,5303,0,0,3,lgbtqia add comment miss crowdfundingcampaign pride unique invention pridemonth collection lgbtqia ally entrepreneurs identify lgbtqia pride
GoFundMe,1831105,1934115,photo,231,110,60,449,"['ORG', 'CARDINAL', 'PERSON', 'DATE', 'GPE']",0,41,4545,214,4,449,lemonade elementary sell robb shooting texas survivor amanda henderson recover robb shooting daniel teammate credit injure mass elementary lemonade pastor sell sweet
GoFundMe,1830824,1933680,link,62,77,6,79,"['ORG', 'CARDINAL', 'PERSON', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'QUANTITY', 'GPE']",0,42,4545,17,0,79,us chris kill six army unit afghanistan grave us mile fall army retired chris six ride foundation fallen foundations
Indiegogo,583071,603115,photo,2,4,1,4,"['DATE', 'ORG']",0,42,5303,0,0,2,brand update tuned brand
Kickstarter,1590673,1588619,link,3,7,0,7,"['ORG', 'PRODUCT', 'CARDINAL', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'ORDINAL', 'GPE']",0,42,4839,1,0,4,irreverent five often sometimes fantasy epic player coop shadow skill cooperative board tabletop 15 quest player master memorable
Indiegogo,583088,603130,video,6,3,2,752,['ORG'],0,43,5303,0,0,6,livall headphone detachable commute ear handsfree handsfree headphone detachable ear
Kickstarter,1590714,1588660,link,3,1,1,5,"['ORG', 'NORP', 'PERSON', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'GPE']",0,43,4839,2,0,5,consider graphic neurotechnology corporate government society scifi anyone attempt novel publish graphic queer african scifi novel graphic queer african scifi upcoming novel cocreator
GoFundMe,1830619,1933590,link,126,99,10,181,"['MONEY', 'CARDINAL', 'PERSON', 'DATE', 'LOC']",0,44,4545,55,0,181,box formula state 33 baby area couple 10000 bay baby formula girlfriend hunt desperately past night instead baby several formula
Kickstarter,1590752,1588691,link,13,1,3,13,"['CARDINAL', 'QUANTITY', 'PRODUCT']",0,44,4839,0,0,13,production engineer maker lower mini scanner blue 3d precision mini scanner 3d mm precision g point wifi speed 160 mm blue scan distance mode resolution weigh
Kickstarter,1590802,1588738,link,4,1,2,4,['PERSON'],0,45,4839,0,0,4,fullcolor marcus graphic character fantastical main must novel drip legend graphic sneaker street wizard myth warrior novel
Indiegogo,583116,603148,link,2,4,0,4,"['PERSON', 'PRODUCT']",0,45,5303,0,0,2,hype musical populele piano test piano hype piano test
GoFundMe,1830062,1933004,link,59,78,3,78,['PERSON'],0,47,4545,11,2,72,lgbtq youth important thrive lgbtq lgbtq connect nonbinary youth youtube tiktok
Indiegogo,583150,603166,video,16,6,6,1575,[],0,47,5303,2,0,18,max pump mosquito outdoor pocketsized mosquito outdoor pocketsized
Indiegogo,583169,603183,video,2,5,1,495,['PRODUCT'],0,48,5303,0,0,2,streaming twitch easily source audio adjust streamer chat control easytouse stream customizable sidekick hello realtime hassle console scene customizable streaming content console
Indiegogo,583186,603196,video,12,4,2,1045,"['CARDINAL', 'ORG']",0,49,5303,4,0,16,twice splach plain offroade motor whether escooter commute fun commuting motor escooter
Indiegogo,583186,603196,link,0,7,0,7,"['CARDINAL', 'DATE']",0,49,5303,0,0,0,2022 gem 2022 miss
Kickstarter,1590959,1588883,video,15,8,2,2206,"['WORK_OF_ART', 'CARDINAL', 'GPE', 'PERSON']",0,49,4839,1,0,16,explorer challenge beyond trail expedition chris rider friendship addiction
Indiegogo,583192,603196,video,3,4,0,788,"['ORG', 'PRODUCT']",0,50,5303,0,0,3,throwback tiny charger cute yet pocketsized computer tiny charger
Indiegogo,583192,603196,photo,0,0,0,0,"['ORG', 'NORP', 'EVENT', 'PERSON', 'DATE', 'GPE', 'MONEY']",0,50,5303,0,0,0,innovation daily youtube iteration generation internet pacific goto presentday invent stem improve simple inventor everyday ntribution steven sharing aapi found hurley groundbreaking spotlight social chen reality chad invention really asian discovery dollar link platform bio science american forward currently throughout islanders pave aapiheritagemonth aapi youtube internet steve cofounder chen heritage
Indiegogo,583192,603196,video,1,4,0,724,['PRODUCT'],0,50,5303,0,0,1,modular handheld user yes mobile finally android gaming gpd console modular handheld user finally android gaming
Kickstarter,1590993,1588915,link,5,3,0,5,"['ORDINAL', 'ORG', 'PERSON']",0,50,4839,0,0,5,romance debut contemporary queer plan author publish romance debut self contemporary queer author print publish
Indiegogo,583192,603196,video,4,2,2,732,['PRODUCT'],0,50,5303,0,0,4,
Indiegogo,583210,603213,video,2,2,0,188,"['CARDINAL', 'DATE', 'ORG', 'PERSON']",0,51,5303,0,0,2,podcast agency marketing listen headphone apple subscribe rainfactory episode official awardwinning drop campaigner industry crowdfundingcampaign podcatcher kaitlyn allnew choice shift cofounder podcast episode episodego 21 drop
Indiegogo,583210,603213,photo,2,1,0,2,['ORG'],0,51,5303,0,0,2,sign guide resource field education reach ultimate plus center
Indiegogo,583210,603213,video,6,1,1,650,"['CARDINAL', 'ORG']",0,51,5303,0,0,6,furniture working tool piece kit interchangeable modular element wfh situation main living 16 invent unique match modular furniture unique piece kit wfh
Kickstarter,1591023,1588941,link,6,0,0,7,"['CARDINAL', 'ORG', 'PERSON']",0,51,4839,1,0,7,struggle balance graphic novel sam cats sliceoflife graphic wrong sam cat magic involve fantasy novel page
Indiegogo,583216,603212,video,37,2,18,1659,"['TIME', 'PRODUCT']",0,52,5303,5,0,42,fold offroade everywhere whether commute fold
Indiegogo,583251,603242,video,9,3,0,1017,"['PERSON', 'PRODUCT']",0,54,5303,1,0,10,electric navee commuter unboxes reviewer futuristic rolling test khanflicks scooter commuter futuristic unbox test
GoFundMe,1828878,1931693,photo,175,193,79,425,"['CARDINAL', 'ORG', 'PERSON']",0,54,4545,171,79,425,elementary robb teacher verified protect gofundmes
Indiegogo,583251,603242,video,3,2,1,627,['DATE'],0,54,5303,0,0,3,roll roll
Indiegogo,583251,603242,video,1,2,1,596,['PERSON'],0,54,5303,0,0,1,sleep tool night sleep tool night
Indiegogo,583274,603264,photo,6,0,1,8,"['ORG', 'NORP', 'EVENT', 'PERSON', 'DATE', 'ORDINAL', 'GPE']",0,55,5303,2,0,8,innovation daily iteration generation pacific goto astronaut presentday stem improve inventor aapi groundbreaking spotlight legacy invention asian discovery platform science american engineer forward currently throughout islanders pave aapiheritagemonth aapi american engineer nasa astronaut heritage
Kickstarter,1591165,1589071,link,9,11,1,11,['ORG'],0,55,4839,0,2,11,measuring progress double track clock consist sourdough sourdough baking
Indiegogo,583274,603264,video,12,2,2,1501,['NORP'],0,56,5303,0,0,12,oven neapolitan inner ease scorpio pizzaiolo pizza unlock oven inner pizzaiolo pizza unlock
Kickstarter,1591328,1589220,link,10,4,0,11,"['DATE', 'PERSON']",0,56,4839,1,0,11,moment rachel dark depression photobook mother capture voice postpartum photographer photobook dark depression postpartum photographer inside secret
Kickstarter,1591388,1589270,link,5,11,0,11,"['CARDINAL', 'DATE', 'ORG', 'MONEY']",0,57,4839,1,2,8,million 800 nearly pledge 2021 benefit fulfil statement public 32 kickstarters benefit statement 2021 profit 2015 pro prioritize focused benefit else corporation public
Kickstarter,1591388,1589270,link,9,3,0,9,['ORG'],0,57,4839,0,0,9,encourage desire balance empire strategic interactive gamess player arc fiction innovative science
GoFundMe,1828212,1930984,link,28,26,18,40,"['ORG', 'GPE']",0,58,4545,6,6,40,del para la una con sean de los gofundmes en texas en texas de affect elementary robb shooting texas verified relief
Indiegogo,583354,603319,video,9,3,2,970,[],0,58,5303,3,0,12,electric reinvent clipper nail mess electric reinvent clipper nail
Indiegogo,583354,603319,video,2,2,0,246,"['CARDINAL', 'ORG', 'MONEY', 'PERSON']",0,58,5303,0,0,2,podcast agency figure marketing lead ensure listen headphone apple subscribe episode official seven process success launchboom hit entire drop campaigner manage podcatcher kevin allnew choice director finish podcast episode episodego drop 20
Kickstarter,1591417,1589296,link,15,7,1,15,[],0,58,4839,0,0,15,jar meal customizable healthy glass kitchen drink prepare planet kitchen jar customizable glass kitchen sustainable
GoFundMe,1828843,1931614,photo,74,48,11,114,"['ORG', 'CARDINAL', 'PERSON', 'DATE', 'FAC', 'GPE']",0,59,4545,40,0,114,item faith battle diagnose april humanity madison york happen garden bucket joel restore square billy gofundmes
Kickstarter,1591454,1589333,link,4,1,0,7,['ORG'],0,59,4839,3,0,7,bracelet conversation piece statement crave icon pleasure
Indiegogo,583437,603385,video,6,2,3,782,['ORG'],0,61,5303,0,0,6,pocketsized develop powerbank pocketsized powerbank
Indiegogo,583437,603385,video,5,1,0,520,['ORG'],0,61,5303,0,0,5,venus lens tiny anamorphic content photographer lens tiny anamorphic
Indiegogo,583459,603403,link,0,0,0,0,['ORG'],0,62,5303,0,0,0,detail tool content announce fundraise expand premium believe equip site audience prove strategy excited education hit reach campaigner plus center introduce education campaigner plus content center site premium excited education specifically campaigner plus content crowdfunde premium announce center site
Indiegogo,583459,603403,photo,3,0,1,3,"['ORG', 'NORP', 'EVENT', 'PERSON', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'DATE', 'GPE']",0,62,5303,0,0,3,innovation daily contribute us iteration generation pacific control goto presentday stem improve pioneer inventor whose pill aapi birth movement groundbreaking research spotlight later dr invention asian min chang discovery platform science american forward currently throughout islanders pave reproductive aapiheritagemonth aapi min chang dr research pioneer ia pill
Indiegogo,583459,603403,video,5,1,0,1093,[],0,62,5303,0,0,5,chef grip sharp prep kitchen elegant versatile enthusiast cooking knife universal chef kitchen enthusiast cooking knife universal
Indiegogo,583459,603403,video,4,1,0,464,['ORG'],0,62,5303,0,0,4,ultrawide lens anamorphic screen content vibe capture vlogger affordable cinematic ultrawide lens anamorphic screen vibe capture affordable cinematic
Kickstarter,1591587,1589453,link,7,6,2,13,"['ORG', 'PERSON']",0,62,4839,6,0,13,survivor monumental gather council sculpture pamela fountain interdisciplinary survivor fountain thrive artwork monumental maintain groundbreaking survivor pamela fountain
Indiegogo,583459,603403,photo,1,0,1,1,"['ORG', 'GPE', 'PERSON']",0,62,5303,0,0,1,sign global strategy excited amazon webinar strategist amy
Indiegogo,583452,603393,video,3,1,1,655,['PRODUCT'],0,63,5303,0,0,3,accessory audio earbud custom podcast control anc detachable immerse builtin fave audio earbud custom podcast control anc builtin fave
Indiegogo,583452,603393,photo,1,4,0,4,"['TIME', 'DATE', 'ORG', 'PERSON']",0,63,5303,0,0,1,25 fit ticket trend grab current excited launchboom becky keynote speak picture ceo summit presentation center healthcare president becky management 2022 vice startup ceo crowdfunde summit center launchboom pst announce highlight ticket speaker inspired step excited becky keynote pm 12 registration industry ready 25th ceo summit crowdfunde center newly
Indiegogo,583452,603393,link,6,0,1,6,"['PRODUCT', 'DATE', 'ORG', 'ORDINAL']",0,63,5303,0,0,6,innovation generator sustainable sneaker solarpowere escooter june crowdfunde 2022 appliance generator heavy duty biodegradable road footwear historic solar scooter
GoFundMe,1827443,1930180,link,47,50,12,54,"['ORG', 'NORP', 'CARDINAL', 'PERSON', 'GPE']",0,63,4545,7,0,54,lack resource highlight aapi recognize awareness action nashville nonprofit organization joseph aapi library hundred leader nashville organization barrier tennessee connection middle joseph nonprofit
Indiegogo,583468,603400,photo,9,4,3,11,"['DATE', 'ORG']",0,64,5303,2,0,11,smash guide content premium amplify forum process site dozen step education crowdfundingcampaign ready specifically plus crowdfunde interactive center introduce education plus center
Kickstarter,1591640,1589494,link,7,3,2,9,"['ORG', 'CARDINAL', 'PERSON', 'DATE', 'ORDINAL']",0,64,4839,2,0,9,brother bestselling merge twin author novel single fifteen unite twin later storm
GoFundMe,1827677,1930414,photo,199,125,12,269,"['ORG', 'EVENT', 'PERSON', 'DATE', 'MONEY']",0,65,4545,70,0,269,already uber tough forward entire driver moore rob shift gofundmes
Indiegogo,583489,603419,video,0,1,0,218,"['CARDINAL', 'ORG', 'PERSON']",0,65,5303,0,0,0,connect podcast lead listen headphone apple subscribe episode official globe fulfillment platform strategy aware matthew shipping drop easyship campaigner podcatcher allnew choice podcast episode 19 episodego drop
Indiegogo,583489,603419,video,6,1,0,884,"['ORG', 'PRODUCT']",0,65,5303,0,0,6,accessible smartphone ii image photography ig recent wildlife stargaze night instagram irl lets scope g sky icymi birdwatching gamechange plus telescope demo capture dwarf enjoy ii telescope dwarf
Kickstarter,1591693,1589548,link,6,1,0,6,"['DATE', 'ORG', 'PRODUCT']",0,65,4839,0,0,6,intelligent magazine journalism commentary literary pack unexpected interview ready 2003 literary essential legacy continue publish carry
Kickstarter,1591704,1589555,link,5,2,0,5,"['WORK_OF_ART', 'ORG', 'PERSON']",0,66,4839,0,0,5,homage dark massive murder death album attack murder bound comic death album spell ticket comic album concert
Indiegogo,583502,603424,video,5,1,2,623,"['WORK_OF_ART', 'DATE', 'PRODUCT']",0,66,5303,1,0,6,qa accessible smartphone peek image us photography ig wildlife stargaze night lets pm sky pdt birdwatching instagramcomindiegogo gamechange telescope capture sneak later enjoy ig pm ii telescope pdt dwarf invent
GoFundMe,1827289,1930021,link,34,31,18,45,"['CARDINAL', 'ORG', 'GPE']",0,67,4545,5,6,45,affect safety shooting buffalo update mass continue centralized hub verify verified trust shoot dead mass ten buffalo affect individual shooting verify mass relief buffalo
GoFundMe,1826818,1929554,link,77,79,14,104,"['DATE', 'PERSON']",0,68,4545,27,0,104,imagine nine age college fall graduate attend 13yearold excited grad elliott robb incredibly attend 13yearold elliot michelle
Indiegogo,583534,603455,video,3,1,1,481,"['ORG', 'QUANTITY']",0,68,5303,0,0,3,content shooting macro cine lens style imaging mm 35 50 24 sirui cine content lense vlogger
GoFundMe,1827076,1929797,video,387,199,199,20190,"['DATE', 'MONEY', 'PERSON']",0,69,4545,411,11,809,tough surprise stranger 75000 despite willing lend michael complete 500 sweet stranger mans must
Indiegogo,583548,603454,video,11,3,2,1479,"['DATE', 'PRODUCT']",0,69,5303,1,0,12,brand electric navee roll scooter brand roll
Indiegogo,583548,603454,photo,3,0,2,3,"['DATE', 'ORG', 'MONEY']",0,69,5303,0,0,3,brand dominate competition apply assistance deadline chance win pitch market 5k stage 16 test ready petition center
Indiegogo,583548,603454,photo,5,1,1,5,"['ORG', 'NORP', 'EVENT', 'PERSON', 'DATE', 'ORDINAL', 'GPE']",0,69,5303,0,0,5,innovation asian daily discovery aapi dr iteration generation pacific groundbreaking platform science american forward wu currently throughout goto islanders presentday spotlight lady stem improve physics invention pave aapiheritagemonth inventor courage push aapi search dr believe science proof forward wheel heritage lady doubt physics dynamic
Indiegogo,583548,603454,video,8,1,7,851,['ORG'],0,69,5303,1,0,9,sofa activity inflate air pump outdoor builtin automatic sofa inflate
Indiegogo,583548,603454,video,4,2,14,978,"['WORK_OF_ART', 'DATE', 'ORG']",0,69,5303,7,0,11,13th movie indie horror alone franchise original hike friday
GoFundMe,1827509,1930217,video,71,341,10,341,[],0,70,4545,25,1,97,helpful person caring tag
Indiegogo,583564,603466,video,5,4,4,648,['ORG'],0,70,5303,0,0,5,usher commuting minimalist commuting
Indiegogo,583564,603466,video,6,2,1,1485,[],0,70,5303,0,1,7,garlic gamechange tool crush rocket kitchen peel garlic gamechange tool crush kitchen peel
Indiegogo,583564,603466,video,3,2,1,230,"['DATE', 'ORG']",0,70,5303,0,1,4,brand website podcast host expert listen headphone followup season apple episode either official plan strategy directly drop campaigner podcatcher allnew choice reason podcast episodego drop season
Indiegogo,583564,603466,link,5,3,1,6,"['ORG', 'CARDINAL', 'DATE', 'QUANTITY', 'MONEY']",0,70,5303,0,1,6,connect foster lead joy discussion case barisieur coffee tea alarm resolve entire prelaunch gather hundred campaigner feedback study grande critical clock discussion education resolve prelaunch center joy success discussion connect feedback resolve prelaunch gather foster investment joy
Kickstarter,1591854,1589695,link,10,9,0,10,"['DATE', 'GPE', 'NORP', 'PERSON']",0,70,4839,0,0,10,citizen united accomplish benjamin states frank photographer word citizen benjamin american society photograph essay
GoFundMe,1827021,1929727,link,33,83,1,83,"['ORG', 'NORP', 'PERSON']",0,71,4545,8,0,41,eat aapi insecurity express panda phillip celebration asian needs 31 phillip eat
Kickstarter,1591901,1589737,link,8,2,1,9,"['ORG', 'CARDINAL', 'PERSON', 'QUANTITY', 'GPE']",0,71,4839,1,0,9,iconic james record band chicago comic indie josh collaboration limitededition punk vinyl 7 comic broken record song james adaptation 7 comic josh single original
Indiegogo,583587,603484,link,4,13,1,13,"['ORG', 'PERSON']",0,71,5303,1,1,6,brand shop connect user state connection transparent trust sit site equity techcrunch becky anywhere interview ceo passion brian accomplish someone center indiegogos ceo becky techcrunch center gig ceo becky center
Indiegogo,583602,603496,photo,3,3,0,3,"['DATE', 'ORG']",0,72,5303,0,0,3,brand competition apply got win gap pitch market hunting develop petition
Indiegogo,583602,603496,video,13,2,2,1037,[],0,72,5303,4,0,17,harness handheld energy charger phone shine clean lets wind backpack charger wind fit
Kickstarter,1591937,1589764,link,11,0,1,11,"['WORK_OF_ART', 'CARDINAL', 'GPE']",0,72,4839,0,0,11,psychedelic source legendary historian americas primary material shed choose source iconic intimate view californias source
Indiegogo,583609,603498,video,2,2,1,643,"['ORG', 'QUANTITY']",0,73,5303,1,0,3,content shooting macro cine lens style imaging mm 35 50 24 sirui unboxing cine content lense vlogger
Indiegogo,583609,603498,link,0,0,0,0,"['PRODUCT', 'ORG', 'PERSON']",0,73,5303,0,0,0,ayaneo handheld gaming especially currently test pc handheld gaming ayaneo handheld pc operating honest ayaneo gaming aaa windows
Kickstarter,1591962,1589785,link,9,0,1,9,['ORG'],0,73,4839,0,0,9,homelessness whose reduce drug living foundation addiction collaborate center sanctuary action rebuild compassion
Indiegogo,583630,603514,video,7,2,7,1316,"['GPE', 'NORP']",0,74,5303,4,0,11,popup mug color pour hot japan beautiful appear mug color pour japanese hot
GoFundMe,1826585,1929263,link,139,85,9,198,"['CARDINAL', 'QUANTITY']",0,75,4545,59,0,198,awareness autism step dad mile walk state autism
GoFundMe,1826286,1928958,video,120,112,12,9071,"['QUANTITY', 'DATE', 'GPE', 'PERSON']",0,76,4545,43,1,164,outside yorker 800 season box vegetable produce alone nicholas lb pantry option farmer fresh 800 produce lb
Kickstarter,1592103,1589924,link,9,2,3,9,[],0,76,4839,0,0,9,revolution possibility prayer magical revolution possible revolution prayer
GoFundMe,1825965,1928625,link,43,32,2,51,"['ORG', 'NORP', 'PERSON', 'DATE', 'GPE']",0,77,4545,8,0,51,brians taylor repay brian possible samaritan forever link taylor rebuild forward brian tornado train
Indiegogo,583663,603517,video,4,3,2,760,"['CARDINAL', 'ORG']",0,77,5303,1,0,5,cleaning wet dry 3in1 spring selfcleaning vacuum roidmi cleaning wet dry 3in1 spring selfcleaning vacuum
GoFundMe,1825965,1928625,photo,42,24,0,48,"['ORG', 'GPE']",0,77,4545,6,0,48,chef feed wisconsin refugee gofundmes
Kickstarter,1592144,1589956,link,9,5,0,9,"['WORK_OF_ART', 'CARDINAL', 'PERSON']",0,77,4839,0,0,9,autistic sons cope traumatic helen autism cope
Indiegogo,583663,603517,link,1,1,0,1,"['CARDINAL', 'DATE']",0,77,5303,0,0,1,season handheld cat stylish gaming pc escooter spring 2022 april 2022 march
Indiegogo,583684,603535,link,2,1,0,2,"['DATE', 'ORG', 'PRODUCT']",0,78,5303,0,0,2,nextgen firewalla firewall hype purple test security network firewalla allinone purple firewalla honest purple breakdown
Indiegogo,583684,603535,video,1,3,0,538,"['ORG', 'NORP', 'CARDINAL', 'EVENT', 'PERSON', 'WORK_OF_ART']",0,78,5303,0,0,1,collectible oneofakind add starwarsday sketch comic lightsaber princess character original cover plus collection collectible wars character 4th star sketch
Kickstarter,1592128,1589937,link,7,1,0,13,"['WORK_OF_ART', 'DATE', 'PERSON']",0,79,4839,6,0,13,tale reader reinvent 1970 manga modern manga peach reimagine print moore
Kickstarter,1592173,1589978,link,4,0,0,4,"['DATE', 'PERSON']",0,80,4839,0,0,4,subscription romance quarterly hardcover box paradise lucy curate box romance quarterly luxury lover
Indiegogo,583667,603494,photo,2,2,1,2,"['DATE', 'ORG', 'MONEY']",0,80,5303,0,0,2,brand dominate competition apply assistance chance win pitch market 5k stage 16 test ready petition center
Indiegogo,583709,603520,video,5,5,1,693,"['CARDINAL', 'ORG']",0,83,5303,0,0,5,cleaning wet dry 3in1 spring selfcleaning vacuum roidmi cleaning wet dry 3in1 spring selfcleaning vacuum
GoFundMe,1825706,1928343,link,50,52,3,63,"['CARDINAL', 'DATE', 'PERSON']",0,83,4545,13,0,63,imagine marathon everyday amputee marathon 102 record marathon 102 attempt really crazy
Indiegogo,583709,603520,link,1,3,0,3,"['WORK_OF_ART', 'ORG', 'PERSON']",0,84,5303,0,0,1,breakfast creek yazebas ruby edition games bed chat anything rpg collaboration possum allnew tabletop director cofounder anything tabletop creek possum roleplaying tabletop interested creek collaboration sit cofounder possum roleplaying chat
Indiegogo,583717,603518,video,6,3,2,708,"['PRODUCT', 'DATE', 'GPE', 'PERSON']",0,84,5303,1,0,7,oldschool berry hollywood legendary edit 1960 editor mike happen howard letter unique editing director letter editing happen
Indiegogo,583717,603518,photo,1,2,0,2,"['TIME', 'CARDINAL', 'DATE', 'ORG']",0,84,5303,0,0,1,expert rsvp linkedin win consultation strategy pdt webinar 11 ready practice 18 zoom page launchready x webinar
Indiegogo,583717,603518,link,1,1,0,1,"['TIME', 'CARDINAL', 'DATE', 'ORG']",0,84,5303,0,0,1,crucial launchready expert draft page cornerstone chance link linkedin maximize attend promising strategy success opportunity notify forward pm select miss directly webinar ready edt strategist feedback consider effective successful zoom submit education directly submit center strategy download matter control engage foster
Indiegogo,583717,603518,photo,10,13,2,13,"['DATE', 'ORG', 'MONEY']",0,84,5303,0,0,10,brand handson competition apply chance win pitch 5k miss 16 teaming petition
Kickstarter,1592261,1590047,link,21,14,1,22,[],0,84,4839,1,0,22,lighting simulate spectrum sun lamp plant elegant indoor plant thoughtfully sun mimic plant fit
GoFundMe,1825063,1927694,link,184,152,77,355,"['CARDINAL', 'DATE', 'PERSON']",0,85,4545,169,2,355,brother legal guardian oneyearold brother seven sister please andrea sibling 7 21 age
Indiegogo,583743,603539,video,8,7,3,676,['PRODUCT'],0,85,5303,0,0,8,pocket smartphone fit stargaze lets expensive beauty birdwatching plus bulky telescope capture enjoy smartphone stargaze birdwatching enjoy
Kickstarter,1592298,1590083,link,13,11,2,14,"['ORG', 'PERSON']",0,85,4839,1,0,14,aspect outreach director comic_strip shine trick publishing publishing page funding element line reward trick choose
Kickstarter,1592298,1590083,link,11,3,0,13,"['WORK_OF_ART', 'CARDINAL', 'PERSON']",0,85,4839,2,0,13,craft combat mini land miniature magical strategy dice combat mini huge bucket focus strategy
Indiegogo,583742,603543,link,4,9,0,9,"['WORK_OF_ART', 'DATE', 'ORG', 'PERSON']",0,86,5303,0,0,4,news excited center techcrunch becky ceo exciting cover ceo becky techcrunch center platform yang ceo becky health andy center
Indiegogo,583742,603543,link,3,1,2,3,"['ORG', 'ORDINAL']",0,86,5303,0,0,3,strategic safety state company initiative becky article partnership fast ceo trust center ceo becky center site ceo female company plan center ecominde focus
GoFundMe,1825028,1927654,video,217,288,27,288,['DATE'],0,86,4545,62,2,281,someone smile reason
Kickstarter,1592344,1590117,link,5,0,0,5,['PERSON'],0,86,4839,0,0,5,disturbing sculpture produce delivery chester controversial surreal introduction willis executive depict thomas hank disturbing delivery controversial surreal sculpture introduction
Indiegogo,583742,603543,link,1,1,1,1,"['ORG', 'GPE', 'PERSON']",0,86,5303,0,0,1,introduce excited blog becky executive officer welcome chief center warm indiegogos ceo becky center indiegogos executive officer welcome chief warm
Indiegogo,583742,603543,photo,6,2,0,8,['PERSON'],0,86,5303,2,0,8,introduce excited blog becky executive officer welcome chief center warm
Indiegogo,583742,603542,link,4,1,0,4,"['CARDINAL', 'PERSON', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'GPE', 'MONEY']",0,87,5303,0,0,4,husk vp ryan trust times los indie success voyager insight especially super angeles competitive haines producer crowdfunde customer direct crowdfund expensive direct spare dollar movie lover might
Indiegogo,583742,603542,video,5,1,1,610,['PRODUCT'],0,87,5303,0,0,5,desire range ice cooling fresh drink temperature cool ice fresh drink cool
Kickstarter,1592383,1590158,link,8,2,0,8,"['DATE', 'GPE', 'PERSON']",0,87,4839,0,0,8,shop mortar wants bakery ontario plant cafe brick shop plant bakery august shop amanda found wright bakery plant 2022 cafe
Indiegogo,583796,603581,video,1,2,0,2,"['CARDINAL', 'DATE', 'ORG', 'PRODUCT']",0,90,5303,0,0,1,motor dual whether notify splach earthhour reduce escooter commute splach motor dual twin scooter splach tour daily allinone twin solution commute perfect
GoFundMe,1824445,1927056,link,52,93,3,93,"['GPE', 'PERSON']",0,90,4545,11,1,64,address rally taylor important struggle teen recognize teenager struggle effort
Indiegogo,583796,603581,video,3,1,1,3,"['ORG', 'QUANTITY', 'PRODUCT']",0,90,5303,0,0,3,navee smooth terrain tubeless notify electric ride earthhour tire reduce scooter escooter navee ultimate suspension capacity front km tire rear motor battery suspension tubeless
Kickstarter,1592501,1590262,link,11,3,0,11,[],0,90,4839,0,0,11,air improve quality indoor carbon monitoring monitor air fresh air quality improve indoor
Indiegogo,583796,603581,link,1,2,0,2,"['EVENT', 'DATE']",0,90,5303,0,0,1,everyday innovation footprint earthday green past collective waste reduce earth green earth green discover ecofriendly roundup innovative
Indiegogo,583796,603581,link,1,0,0,1,"['EVENT', 'DATE']",0,91,5303,0,0,1,earthday green earth green earth green discover ecofriendly roundup innovative
Indiegogo,583815,603596,video,6,1,5,1255,"['EVENT', 'DATE', 'ORG']",0,91,5303,2,0,8,everyday innovation earth longterm honbike round environment us earthday green lets ecofriendly observe sustainable positive earthhour sonder lifestyle sol everyday earth green
Indiegogo,583815,603596,video,4,1,0,5,"['EVENT', 'DATE', 'ORG']",0,91,5303,1,0,5,everyday innovation earth longterm honbike round environment earthday green campaigns lets ecofriendly observe sustainable positive earthhour sonder lifestyle sol everyday earth green
GoFundMe,1824252,1926861,link,46,60,4,60,"['PERSON', 'QUANTITY', 'LOC', 'GPE']",0,91,4545,10,1,57,mile store grocery close 20 insecurity farmer produce farmer identify nc fresh chloe produce moore
Indiegogo,583815,603596,video,9,5,2,569,['PRODUCT'],0,91,5303,1,0,10,musical guide lead keyboard chord skill populele perform piano pad unique improve fun piano lead performing fun
Indiegogo,583815,603596,link,3,1,0,3,"['ORG', 'DATE', 'GPE', 'ORDINAL']",0,92,5303,0,0,3,exciting exclusive crowdfunde 2022 maker access station meal sandwich internet lightweight japan slice g bread release single
Kickstarter,1592583,1590344,link,8,2,1,8,"['ORDINAL', 'CARDINAL', 'ORG', 'PERSON']",0,92,4839,0,0,8,plush fiber cotton towel upcycle sustainability luxury nebia towel textile upcycled worlds towel breakthrough
Indiegogo,583825,603600,video,3,2,0,411,"['DATE', 'ORG', 'NORP']",0,93,5303,0,0,3,breakfast cuttingedge creek oneofakind yazebas exchange sliceoflife queer mechanic fantasy bed happen possum tabletop roleplaying sliceoflife ttrpg cuttingedge queer happen gaming fantasy
Indiegogo,583843,603610,video,1,2,0,3686,"['ORG', 'PRODUCT', 'PERSON', 'TIME', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'DATE']",0,93,5303,0,0,1,jay breakfast creek exciting sleepaway yazebas fave wanderhome games bed throwback awardwinning funding hit rpg dragon possum editorial tabletop ttrpg conversation ttrpgs director within author inspiration jay breakfast creek exciting sleepaway yazebas fave wanderhome games bed awardwinning funding hit rpg dragon possum editorial tabletop ttrpgs director within author inspiration
Indiegogo,583843,603610,video,5,1,2,1790,['TIME'],0,93,5303,1,0,6,artisanstyle obsess cream ice within comfort artisanstyle cream ice within minute
GoFundMe,1824289,1926890,photo,72,106,2,106,"['ORG', 'CARDINAL', 'PERSON', 'TIME', 'GPE', 'MONEY']",0,93,4545,10,0,82,zack arrest shooter nearby police brooklyn bravery update involve security flag york 50k neighbor several grateful reward subway zack apparent 36 anonymous inherent shine 30 shooter samantha brooklyn awareness morning security jersey organize screen donation lisa miraculously spotlight jason catch 2d gofundmes
Kickstarter,1592636,1590402,link,4,4,2,6,['WORK_OF_ART'],0,93,4839,2,0,6,possibility mess fill human action steel saga fantasy epic motorcycle action anarchy queer dragon sword
Indiegogo,583843,603610,video,6,1,3,620,['PRODUCT'],0,93,5303,1,0,7,foldable honbike assist smoothsailing drive frame ride
Kickstarter,1592636,1590402,link,16,8,4,20,"['TIME', 'LOC']",0,93,4839,4,0,20,foldable kayak assemble minute oru origami kayak simple lake box fold accessible kayak boat simple minute
Indiegogo,583841,603598,video,3,2,1,708,['PRODUCT'],0,94,5303,0,0,3,speaker corner action simple affordable speaker corner
Kickstarter,1592659,1590425,link,35,7,4,39,['ORG'],0,94,4839,4,0,39,ergonomic oled measurement measure display fast tape digital robotic measure professional tape digital connect laser app line measure mobile projection tape digital integrate ready
Indiegogo,583841,603598,video,3,4,3,525,['PRODUCT'],0,94,5303,1,0,4,round wall green veggie installation garden earthhour healthy actually herb enjoy garden wall
Kickstarter,1592659,1590425,link,4,5,3,7,[],0,94,4839,3,0,7,starter tool dough kitchen temperature starter warm sourdough starter bread bake active sourdough
Indiegogo,583860,603609,video,7,7,3,1027,['ORG'],0,95,5303,0,0,7,aid olive earbud adaptive usa enhance union hearing conversation bluetooth builtin invent aid adaptive earbud hearing bluetooth builtin
Indiegogo,583860,603609,video,13,2,2,1463,[],0,95,5303,2,0,15,motion detection drive 4k dashcam motion detection drive 4k dashcam
Indiegogo,583860,603609,video,3,1,3,580,['PRODUCT'],0,95,5303,0,0,3,mirror motorcycle 7 signal ride pack helmet gear led motorcycle smoothsailing ride pack ensure helmet gear led
Indiegogo,583863,603610,video,5,1,1,626,"['CARDINAL', 'PRODUCT']",0,96,5303,1,0,6,skill musical populele improve allinone lead keyboard skill improve allinone lead keyboard
Indiegogo,583863,603610,video,6,1,2,781,['ORG'],0,96,5303,0,0,6,shaver add essential shaver add essential
Indiegogo,583863,603610,video,4,2,1,635,"['QUANTITY', 'DATE', 'ORG', 'NORP']",0,96,5303,0,0,4,anamorphic content shoot 75 cinematic lens ig instagram imaging mm excited photographer mindblowing instagramcomindiegogo plus sirui footage takeover siruis lens anamorphic ig 75 shoot takeover mm
Indiegogo,583863,603610,video,4,1,2,900,"['QUANTITY', 'PRODUCT']",0,96,5303,0,0,4,max solve 30 motor dual road drive commuter gokart mph speed scooter obstacle gokart scooter
Indiegogo,583863,603610,link,0,1,1,1,"['WORK_OF_ART', 'ORG', 'PERSON']",0,96,5303,0,0,0,xfoil deep edition sit watersport anything conversation dive xfoil anything watersport introduce xfoil allow anything flying sit exclusive surfing campaigner
GoFundMe,1824162,1926773,link,72,65,6,95,['PERSON'],0,97,4545,23,0,95,muscular opportunity dystrophy diagnose riley custom costume wheelchair custom wheelchair ride wise hello costume riley
Kickstarter,1592769,1590522,link,9,5,4,10,"['ORG', 'NORP']",0,97,4839,1,0,10,radical type library collective enable wool creation yarn source british wool library empower farmer fully consumer wool yarn british
GoFundMe,1823640,1926241,video,35,48,6,10069,"['CARDINAL', 'GPE', 'LOC', 'PERSON']",0,98,4545,11,1,47,mile central benefit park record runner ukraine national mine park yorks record central mile upend ukraine oz
Kickstarter,1592815,1590571,link,3,3,0,3,"['ORG', 'CARDINAL', 'DATE', 'GPE']",0,98,4839,0,0,3,1980 supernatural lucky dangerous games orleans exciting duck magical quarter dark cooperative dark narrative 1980s quarter orleans
GoFundMe,1823475,1926077,link,74,109,9,125,"['MONEY', 'GPE', 'NORP', 'PERSON']",0,99,4545,40,11,125,german rally shepherd shoot connecticut twice 20000 almost shoot internet shoot official establish behalf medical staff cost
Kickstarter,1592838,1590588,link,5,4,1,5,"['ORDINAL', 'CARDINAL', 'ORG', 'PERSON']",0,99,4839,0,0,5,plush textile upcycled perfectly effectively nebia soft towel skin breakthrough sustainability luxury nebia towel textile upcycled worlds towel breakthrough
GoFundMe,1823313,1925918,link,29,52,5,52,"['CARDINAL', 'PERSON']",0,100,4545,8,0,37,wildlife outdoor transition volunteer wildlife volunteer inside dozen hr job fulltime actual inside
Kickstarter,1592930,1590685,link,4,0,2,9,"['GPE', 'PERSON']",0,100,4839,1,4,9,domestic document india trafficking sex truly nepal cry sharma silence domestic document india trafficking sex nepal
Indiegogo,583960,603673,video,9,6,3,979,"['DATE', 'ORG']",0,100,5303,1,0,10,fat fibre heavy terrain lightweight smoothsailing ride carbon tire frame clunky fibre smooth fat frame ride carbon terrain lightweight tire
Kickstarter,1592930,1590685,link,14,36,0,36,['ORG'],0,100,4839,3,0,17,tool safety view alter public comment hide automatically platform conduct manage conversation report trust comment improve commitment excited comment tool conversation important update platform manage
GoFundMe,1823554,1926148,link,37,37,1,44,"['PERSON', 'DATE', 'ORG', 'GPE']",0,101,4545,7,0,44,easter deserve basket easter basket michigan teen easter hi mari 2022 mi 14 flint
Indiegogo,583964,603668,link,0,7,0,7,['EVENT'],0,101,5303,1,0,1,string overload purrini playhouse toy modular bit nationalpetday bacon cheese kitty cute test pet cats paradise purrini playmate modular cat purrini playmate toy pet structure
Kickstarter,1592966,1590718,link,8,0,0,8,"['NORP', 'CARDINAL', 'PERSON', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'GPE']",0,101,4839,0,0,8,graphic novel stealth ninja epic 600 thru sprawl shadow graphic subway saga flow page
Indiegogo,583972,603661,link,0,5,0,5,"['DATE', 'PRODUCT']",0,103,5303,0,0,0,string overload purrini playhouse toy modular bit bacon cheese kitty cute test caturday pet cats paradise purrini playmate modular cat purrini playmate toy pet structure
GoFundMe,1822914,1925501,link,50,69,5,69,"['EVENT', 'DATE', 'PERSON']",0,103,4545,19,0,69,doll syndrome syndrome preschooler teach toy syndrome spread awareness joy sarah
Indiegogo,583972,603661,video,2,3,0,3,"['ORG', 'PRODUCT']",0,103,5303,1,0,3,notify interesting fun modern earthhour diaper ecofriendly diaper diaper interesting fun
Indiegogo,583972,603661,video,9,6,3,903,"['TIME', 'DATE', 'ORG']",0,103,5303,0,0,9,discover bad dry speed dryer minute hair fave bad dry speed dryer minute hair
Indiegogo,583932,603617,video,4,9,1,605,"['QUANTITY', 'ORG']",0,104,5303,0,0,4,anamorphic content fave lens imaging closeup subject develop frame sirui capture subject lens anamorphic closeup frame 75 capture mm
GoFundMe,1822712,1925295,photo,26,37,2,37,"['ORG', 'CARDINAL', 'PERCENT', 'GPE', 'MONEY']",0,104,4545,5,0,31,dad item fundraise sick texas catalog sell item tool piece 1200 real enjoy 40 instead scoop bug 12 drag catalog sell exactly cut stop giant neighborhood gofundmes
Indiegogo,583932,603617,video,5,6,3,871,"['DATE', 'ORG']",0,105,5303,1,0,6,fat fibre heavy terrain lightweight smoothsailing ride carbon tire frame clunky fibre smooth fat frame ride carbon terrain lightweight tire
GoFundMe,1822517,1925078,link,37,76,7,76,"['ORG', 'GPE', 'PERSON']",0,105,4545,17,0,54,period found confident service texas teen period address poverty teen junior taylor grand texas menstruation
Kickstarter,1592882,1590630,link,12,12,1,12,['ORG'],0,105,4839,0,0,12,steel misen strong lifetime nonstick carbon cast pan steel misen carbon pan forever iron strong naturally nonstick versatile cast pan
Indiegogo,583950,603631,photo,1,1,1,1,"['WORK_OF_ART', 'CARDINAL', 'DATE', 'ORG']",0,106,5303,0,0,1,sign enter performance launchready engage best apply draft page cornerstone april indiegogos win consultation maximize attend strategy visitor please order attendee draw learning prelaunch miss mark webinar 35 11 ready eligible understanding member effective practice successful calendar submit page launchready x webinar
Indiegogo,583950,603631,video,4,7,1,589,"['TIME', 'ORG', 'PRODUCT']",0,106,5303,0,0,4,anticipate pro czur scan gadget entire minute cool stuff plus unboxing czur react entire scanner unboxing minute pro
Indiegogo,583950,603631,photo,2,0,0,2,"['ORG', 'PRODUCT', 'CARDINAL', 'TIME', 'DATE']",0,106,5303,0,0,2,crucial launchready expert draft page cornerstone chance link linkedin maximize attend promising strategy success opportunity notify forward zoom pm select miss innovator webinar ready edt strategist feedback consider effective successful directly submit page launchready x webinar
GoFundMe,1822435,1924993,link,73,53,2,93,"['ORG', 'CARDINAL', 'PERSON', 'DATE', 'QUANTITY', 'MONEY']",0,106,4545,20,0,93,mile duo antonio san 10000 bank antonio del san 10000 bank challenge sam
Kickstarter,1592923,1590661,photo,9,8,1,10,"['ORG', 'PERSON', 'TIME', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'DATE', 'ORDINAL']",0,106,4839,1,0,10,april register 7 conversation reframd importance supportive thursday innovation 7th ticket area importance excited swift convince 8 topic exciting challenge discussion development process thursday pm finance expect hunt particular different panel question welcome evening answer april 6 valuable ago building startup heather partner available attention opportunity 2022 reframd accompany clear event
Kickstarter,1592923,1590661,link,5,5,1,5,[],0,106,4839,0,0,5,pressure illness commentary mental navigate depression cure press worry drift simple cassette
GoFundMe,1821986,1924542,link,23,26,3,26,"['CARDINAL', 'ORG', 'GPE']",0,107,4545,1,2,26,affect sacramento centralized shooting hub verified safety update verify mass continue trust sacramento six shoot dead downtown affect sacramento shooting verify mass downtown relief
Indiegogo,583962,603635,photo,6,5,0,7,"['ORG', 'PRODUCT', 'CARDINAL', 'PERSON', 'DATE']",0,107,5303,1,0,7,brand price luxury ecommerce global fulfillment ship easyship quickly partner solution e
GoFundMe,1821986,1924542,video,138,98,13,14135,['PERSON'],0,107,4545,68,0,206,deserve
Indiegogo,583962,603635,video,13,3,2,803,"['CARDINAL', 'QUANTITY', 'PRODUCT']",0,107,5303,1,0,14,mile emergency monster extra 12 single 18 battery pro backup station 12 battery backup
Indiegogo,583962,603635,video,1,1,2,554,"['CARDINAL', 'PRODUCT']",0,107,5303,1,0,2,twice typically size plus pretty motor wild eins twice typically size motor wild
Indiegogo,583962,603635,link,2,2,0,4,"['QUANTITY', 'DATE', 'ORG']",0,107,5303,2,0,4,notable invention sneak peek april 2022 40 battery mph personal else spring trainer scooter
Kickstarter,1592951,1590687,link,5,6,0,6,['CARDINAL'],0,107,4839,0,0,5,theater dark immersive perform flashlight puppet theater dark immersive
Indiegogo,583962,603635,video,2,4,1,714,['ORG'],0,108,5303,4,0,6,smoker rib indoor kitchen pellet outdoor comfort reimagine smoke firstbuild fave smoker pellet outdoor reimagine indoor
Indiegogo,583962,603635,video,1,0,1,398,"['ORG', 'PRODUCT']",0,108,5303,0,0,1,aid adaptive olive question builtin earbud got hearing bluetooth upcoming munity union conversation aid olive adaptive earbud hearing max 2in1
Indiegogo,583979,603646,link,2,0,0,3,"['ORDINAL', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'ORG', 'PERSON']",0,108,5303,1,0,3,xfoil question deep sit burn anything dive xfoil anything watersport introduce xfoil allow anything flying sit exclusive surfing campaigner
GoFundMe,1822136,1924699,link,167,84,7,247,"['ORDINAL', 'DATE', 'MONEY', 'PERSON']",0,108,4545,80,0,247,decade birthday kai research decade 15yearold choose birthday gilbert decade kai martin past 15 begin birthday
Kickstarter,1593024,1590752,link,7,3,0,8,"['DATE', 'GPE', 'PERSON']",0,108,4839,1,0,8,psychological among multicultural london teen friendship psychological innocent thirteen swell
Indiegogo,584041,603684,video,4,3,0,618,"['CARDINAL', 'DATE', 'PERSON']",0,111,5303,1,1,6,purrini fourlegged configuration modular custom cat diy anything kitty playground tree caturday castle custom playground kitty diy
Kickstarter,1593259,1590975,link,6,3,1,6,['GPE'],0,112,4839,0,0,6,photography color london interview photography negative colour photography colour interview
Indiegogo,584132,603763,video,28,3,1,3680,"['ORG', 'PRODUCT', 'PERSON', 'TIME', 'WORK_OF_ART']",0,113,5303,2,0,30,jay breakfast creek exciting sleepaway yazebas fave wanderhome games bed awardwinning funding hit rpg dragon possum editorial tabletop ttrpgs director within author inspiration ig creek possum
Indiegogo,584132,603763,video,7,3,7,915,['ORG'],0,113,5303,1,0,8,storage subscription alternative total plugandplay app cloud security control fee privacy subscription cloud alternative
Indiegogo,584132,603763,video,6,2,0,467,['TIME'],0,113,5303,0,0,6,forever international traditional czur scanner scan entire pack minute goodbye bulky entire minute scan
Indiegogo,584132,603763,video,2,6,2,625,"['QUANTITY', 'PRODUCT']",0,113,5303,0,0,2,front mode escooter acceleration race rear suspension tire segway escooter
Kickstarter,1593330,1591038,link,6,7,0,7,"['CARDINAL', 'NORP']",0,113,4839,0,0,6,couple anonymous client horror custom agree couple mysterious control client spiral
Indiegogo,584132,603763,video,1,2,1,604,"['DATE', 'ORG']",0,113,5303,0,0,1,builtin flashlight emergency supply corner mosquito outdoor repellant flashlight emergency supply mosquito repellant
Indiegogo,584132,603763,video,4,4,4,1223,"['PRODUCT', 'ORG', 'PERSON']",0,114,5303,0,0,4,wallet builtin ig marshall currently sustainable miss solar inspiration bank sonder sol inventor panel sustainable wallet bank sonder sol solar
Indiegogo,584146,603774,video,2,3,2,381,"['DATE', 'ORG']",0,114,5303,0,0,2,add smooth aerodynamic commuter ride 2022 fast cut wind tube fun smooth ride aerodynamic fast tube fun
Indiegogo,584146,603774,video,9,4,1,667,"['ORG', 'NORP']",0,114,5303,2,0,11,press brew messy classic capra french reimagine coffee cleanup press reimagine french
Indiegogo,584146,603774,video,13,2,12,1426,"['DATE', 'ORG', 'PERSON']",0,114,5303,7,0,20,panel accessory qa wallet environmentallyfriendly peek builtin fave ig pm later sustainable et solar instagramcomindiegogo crowdfunde bank sneak sonder sol inspiration inventor ig pt pm sustainable wallet solar
Indiegogo,584146,603774,video,0,2,0,170,"['WORK_OF_ART', 'DATE', 'ORG', 'ORDINAL']",0,114,5303,0,0,0,podcast question listen season worth apple subscribe episode official whether date currency firstever drop podcatcher frequently choice podcasts clip event podcast episode episodego drop season
Indiegogo,584146,603774,photo,5,2,0,5,"['PERSON', 'DATE', 'ORG', 'PRODUCT']",0,114,5303,0,0,5,roll vision movie projector entertainment laser ust 4k comfort buzz triple mine literature store projector reply yesterday laser et andy ust 4k trust
Kickstarter,1593360,1591064,link,25,5,2,30,"['LOC', 'GPE', 'NORP']",0,114,4839,5,0,30,near russia war journalist zone ukraine journalist european russia lifeline ukraine
GoFundMe,1821237,1923660,video,82,92,13,582205,"['ORDINAL', 'PERSON']",0,114,4545,56,0,138,glass jonathans color pair please jonathan god credit bless
Indiegogo,584162,603790,video,4,5,2,738,"['WORK_OF_ART', 'ORG']",0,115,5303,0,2,6,anywhere reusable goto bottle earthhour builtin carry goto bottle carry
Indiegogo,584162,603790,photo,2,1,0,2,"['ORG', 'CARDINAL', 'PERSON', 'DATE', 'ORDINAL', 'GPE']",0,115,5303,0,0,2,chef female role surround council crenn vision plantbase snack step culinary michelin confident vitabowl dominique internationalwomensday pioneer spends restaurant star highprotein chef everyday international surround womens crenn vision lawyer michelin confident vitabowl dominique pioneer visionary restaurant star
Indiegogo,584162,603790,video,4,2,0,553,['DATE'],0,115,5303,0,1,5,brand roll eins brand roll
Indiegogo,584162,603790,video,11,2,3,1022,['ORG'],0,115,5303,0,0,11,cart fold anywhere luggage cart heavy anywhere universal lets luggage
Kickstarter,1593404,1591106,link,14,7,0,15,"['WORK_OF_ART', 'ORG', 'PERSON']",0,115,4839,1,0,15,version craig russell legendary classic adapt opera novel illustrate graphic carmen director p carmen novel graphic classic arizona craig partnership adapt opera russell p
Kickstarter,1593404,1591106,link,11,2,6,12,[],0,115,4839,1,0,12,serial struggle marriage notorious comic killer serial struggle dark marriage notorious comedy killer
Kickstarter,1593453,1591152,link,1,4,0,4,['ORG'],0,116,4839,1,0,2,afro membership obsess assistant role desk museum question exclusive customer coworker fairchild graduate afro membership obsess assistant role desk museum question exclusive customer coworker
Kickstarter,1593495,1591197,link,3,5,1,5,[],0,117,4839,0,0,3,romance crush scifi romance fiction science
Kickstarter,1593558,1591252,link,7,6,0,7,"['NORP', 'PERSON', 'ORDINAL', 'GPE', 'LOC']",0,118,4839,0,0,7,generation immigration americans entrepreneurship mother origin jean american concept blend south wish refugee
GoFundMe,1820984,1923478,link,127,148,11,182,"['DATE', 'PERSON']",0,119,4545,53,2,182,kai past exactly wish birthday research present teen birthday kai
Indiegogo,584217,603818,link,5,3,0,7,"['QUANTITY', 'DATE', 'ORG', 'ORDINAL']",0,119,5303,1,1,7,exciting trainer exclusive piano ai personal invention escooter april 2022 40 battery mph personal else spring trainer scooter
Indiegogo,584217,603818,video,1,2,0,242,"['CARDINAL', 'ORG']",0,119,5303,0,1,2,podcast indemand best listen headphone apple subscribe episode official gap postcampaign strategy funding difference bridge drop crowdfundingcampaign campaigner breakdown commerce podcatcher allnew choice practice solution podcast episode episodego drop 16
Kickstarter,1593580,1591269,link,7,2,0,7,"['ORG', 'NORP', 'CARDINAL', 'PERSON', 'GPE']",0,119,4839,0,0,7,poetry literary edition present star letterpress rise storm magnetic please literature rise edition star ukrainian letterpress limited
Indiegogo,584217,603818,video,2,4,1,500,"['ORG', 'PERSON', 'TIME', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'DATE']",0,119,5303,1,0,3,jay breakfast 330 creek exciting sleepaway yazebas fave ig wanderhome games bed awardwinning funding hit pm rpg dragon possum instagramcomindiegogo editorial tabletop pt ttrpgs director within wednesday author inspiration breakfast ig ttrpg 330 pm et bed yazebas
Kickstarter,1593580,1591269,link,13,4,3,15,"['GPE', 'NORP', 'PERSON']",0,119,4839,2,0,15,brooklyn app dating queer jewish fail portrait brooklyn jelly romantic queer comedy bean intimacy dating trial pivotal crave
Indiegogo,584217,603818,video,2,3,0,612,['ORG'],0,120,5303,1,1,4,body chronic waterproof develop patch ache soft pain flexible manage body chronic waterproof patch ache soft pain flexible manage
GoFundMe,1820732,1923231,link,117,84,5,151,"['EVENT', 'DATE', 'GPE', 'PERSON']",0,120,4545,33,1,151,dad 6 cheer games eyesight ago march dad blind sweet 16 tomorrow
Kickstarter,1593619,1591312,link,12,4,6,20,"['CARDINAL', 'PERSON']",0,120,4839,8,0,20,type diabetic trial noah chronicle type type search diabetic wife
Indiegogo,584228,603816,video,7,3,0,529,"['TIME', 'DATE', 'NORP']",0,121,5303,1,0,8,breakfast cuttingedge creek yazebas sliceoflife queer games mechanic fantasy bed hit shoutout happen possum tabletop within roleplaying sliceoflife ttrpg cuttingedge queer happen gaming fantasy
Kickstarter,1593638,1591329,link,16,11,1,22,['GPE'],0,121,4839,6,0,22,photography wet aka blackness afrofuturism plate america magic portrait photography wet afrofuturism blackness plate exploration
Kickstarter,1593638,1591329,link,7,4,2,9,"['NORP', 'PERSON']",0,121,4839,2,0,9,german village person queer return move land move queer trouble
Indiegogo,584225,603802,video,16,4,2,1439,['ORG'],0,122,5303,1,2,19,foldable cart goexplore far sweat heavy anywhere universal lets distance luggage cart heavy anywhere universal lets luggage
Indiegogo,584225,603802,video,9,2,0,973,['ORG'],0,122,5303,1,2,12,front goexplore safety rear protect class speed ride helmet builtin integrate front safety rear protect ride speed helmet builtin integrate
Kickstarter,1593634,1591322,photo,9,4,2,12,[],0,122,4839,3,0,12,subscription pepper service chili rare hot door deliver
Indiegogo,584225,603802,video,4,2,2,521,[],0,122,5303,2,2,8,panel goexplore sonder bank wallet sol builtin solar panel bank wallet builtin solar
Indiegogo,584225,603802,photo,3,1,0,4,"['EVENT', 'DATE', 'ORG', 'PERSON']",0,122,5303,0,1,4,brand enough earth move resource solve fellowship wait leverage outline compostable brush suzan hernandez mamap perfect ecofriendly problem forward research confident sustainable stage digital internationalwomensday grad fully clean return everyday enough move international graduate solve fellowship wait womens outline suzan hernandez mamap perfect problem forward confident stage
Indiegogo,584225,603802,video,8,4,2,2240,['TIME'],0,122,5303,2,1,11,artisanstyle obsess cream ice within comfort artisanstyle cream ice within minute
GoFundMe,1820689,1923160,link,48,97,3,97,"['ORG', 'DATE', 'GPE', 'NORP']",0,124,4545,6,1,55,affect centralized verified texas hub safety update verify wildfire continue trust displace destroy resident spread texas wildfire texans recover rebuild texas verify wildfire relief
GoFundMe,1820290,1922756,video,135,115,30,10760,"['CARDINAL', 'GPE', 'NORP']",0,125,4545,73,2,210,displace 600 generosity poland ukrainian bear teddy bears shelter ukrainian teddy
Indiegogo,584269,603813,photo,4,1,0,4,"['ORG', 'PRODUCT', 'CARDINAL', 'TIME', 'DATE', 'MONEY']",0,125,5303,0,0,4,sign draft page cornerstone worth chance linkedin win pst1 attend strategy entire pm select innovator prize webinar 35 ready 50 plus spot effective est successful zoom page 23rd 130 champion ampst engagement pm 2022 march webinar 1030 effective wednesday zoom
Indiegogo,584269,603813,video,5,3,0,553,"['DATE', 'ORG']",0,125,5303,0,2,7,hike alone franchise friday films happen 13th
Indiegogo,584269,603813,video,1,2,2,592,"['ORG', 'PRODUCT']",0,125,5303,0,1,2,question trainer altis got link comment upcoming bio tv munity aipowered prelaunch drop fitness personalized ai tap personal conversation workout altis ai personal trainer
Kickstarter,1593772,1591444,link,9,4,1,10,"['CARDINAL', 'QUANTITY', 'PRODUCT']",0,125,4839,1,0,10,shot character main 16 mm leather inch jellyfish shoot surveillance 16 mm
Kickstarter,1593826,1591504,link,9,4,0,9,"['WORK_OF_ART', 'NORP', 'PERSON']",0,126,4839,0,0,9,graphic memory novel legacy graphic novel tale mythology greek memory gorgeous reimagine legacy
Indiegogo,584277,603818,video,14,2,3,1650,"['QUANTITY', 'PRODUCT']",0,126,5303,1,0,15,lb kayak size 7 tent pack lightweight weigh
Indiegogo,584277,603818,photo,2,1,0,2,"['ORG', 'CARDINAL', 'PERSON', 'DATE', 'GPE']",0,126,5303,0,0,2,president numerous seem force found scary michele process entrepreneurship important internationalwomensday ready clearco stranger iterate cofounder everyday international president seem womens force scary michele process important ready clearco jump iterate cofounder
GoFundMe,1820542,1922997,link,42,90,7,90,"['CARDINAL', 'DATE', 'ORG']",0,127,4545,3,9,54,closely safety monitor southwest accident official update university platform hub verify bus trust accident condition dead 9 bus critical affect accident commit bus university southwest
Indiegogo,584290,603816,photo,5,2,2,5,"['ORG', 'EVENT', 'CARDINAL', 'PERSON', 'DATE', 'GPE']",0,127,5303,0,0,5,aid syria brand energy accessible whose california passionate teamed popular enthusiast whether ago andrea alum seek amazon sustainable backyard refugee nepal igg solar solarpowered lantern showcase natural launchpad anna worker disaster available solution womens 2011 andrea amazon inspiring inflatable solarpowered solar 2017 discover unique anna launchpad patent successful available inventor innovative
Indiegogo,584290,603816,video,4,3,2,919,[],0,127,5303,0,1,5,foldable assist honbike drive frame
Kickstarter,1593850,1591525,link,16,6,0,16,"['CARDINAL', 'PRODUCT']",0,127,4839,0,0,16,tool code teach programmable drone education programmable lesson 7 sensor
Indiegogo,584290,603816,link,6,1,0,7,"['ORG', 'MONEY']",0,127,5303,0,1,7,company advance excited accelerate clearco growth blog capital clearco advance allow capital base date
Indiegogo,584290,603816,video,4,3,1,965,"['CARDINAL', 'DATE', 'ORG']",0,127,5303,0,2,6,litter fourlegged automatic box scoop cat maybe feline caturday clean box scoop cat litter automatic
Indiegogo,584306,603813,video,1,3,0,218,"['CARDINAL', 'ORG']",0,128,5303,0,1,2,podcast conversion listen headphone apple subscribe episode official optimize audience strategy manager management drop campaigner podcatcher allnew choice stop podcast episode 15 episodego drop
Kickstarter,1593879,1591550,link,8,7,0,8,"['CARDINAL', 'ORG']",0,128,4839,0,0,8,civilization demon board cooperative defend 12 task four player bad zodiac intelligent board cooperative 14 enemy player
Indiegogo,584306,603813,photo,1,1,0,1,"['ORG', 'PRODUCT', 'EVENT', 'PERSON', 'DATE']",0,128,5303,0,0,1,kenison fashion emily robecurls viral tiktok internationalwomensday hack spends successfully inventor everyday kenison international womens real emily robecurls fast test feedback improve actually lean iterate cofounder customer inventor
Indiegogo,584306,603813,video,6,4,1,657,"['DATE', 'ORG']",1,128,5303,1,2,9,brewing joy custom style dual barisieur coffee perfect heating brew tea resolve steel pourover temp ultimate wake grande large clean tea brew wake coffee
Indiegogo,584306,603813,video,1,2,0,518,"['CARDINAL', 'PERSON']",0,129,5303,0,1,2,material level goexplore handbag backpack sustainable convert essential convert
Indiegogo,584306,603813,video,1,3,0,562,"['DATE', 'ORDINAL']",0,129,5303,1,1,3,campfire camping warm season camp goexplore heat reflect wind block enjoy heat campfire camping season
Indiegogo,584318,603816,video,3,2,0,508,"['ORG', 'PRODUCT']",0,129,5303,0,0,3,everyday minimal goexplore aesthetic ultra imagine bulky slim wallet function gear none ultra slim wallet
Kickstarter,1593915,1591589,link,7,2,0,7,"['ORG', 'GPE', 'LOC']",0,129,4839,0,0,7,environmental river musical tradition threat river yuma sonic journey depth river musical present
Indiegogo,584318,603816,video,3,1,0,4,"['CARDINAL', 'ORG', 'ORDINAL']",0,129,5303,0,1,4,sign posture trainer comfy stylish notify finally fix goexplore posture comfortable stylish trainer style immediate clothe comfort function maximum wear
Indiegogo,584318,603816,video,1,2,0,329,['ORG'],0,129,5303,0,1,2,brand potential consumer accelerate acquisition announce brand growth ecommerce consumer accelerate
Indiegogo,584318,603816,video,1,4,0,803,"['CARDINAL', 'DATE', 'ORG']",0,129,5303,0,1,2,litter fourlegged automatic box scoop cat maybe feline caturday clean box scoop cat litter automatic
Indiegogo,584355,603835,video,1,4,0,583,"['ORDINAL', 'ORG', 'PRODUCT']",0,131,5303,0,0,1,enter ayaneo ryzen handheld trigger gaming sensor ultimate hall amd 7 joystick aaa windows handheld gaming gamer
Indiegogo,584379,603847,photo,8,5,1,12,"['GPE', 'PERSON']",0,132,5303,4,0,12,solidarity war standwithukraine ukraine ongoing e ukraine
GoFundMe,1820041,1922428,photo,67,111,11,111,"['ORG', 'PRODUCT', 'CARDINAL', 'PERSON', 'MONEY']",0,132,4545,24,1,92,outside navy lifeline us possible rally veteran patriotic heartbroken forward 50 100k kenny scooter 50 forward veteran kenny scooter gofundmes
Kickstarter,1594051,1591700,link,18,6,2,21,"['LOC', 'GPE', 'NORP']",0,132,4839,3,0,21,potter craft indigenous ceramic traditional japan plate unique japan plate indigenous traditional japanese group
Indiegogo,584379,603847,video,2,1,0,826,"['CARDINAL', 'ORG', 'PRODUCT']",0,132,5303,0,1,3,brewing oneofakind question joy got custom style dual lover barisieur coffee upcoming brew heating munity resolve steel pourover grande conversation large clean brewing grande barisieur platform
Indiegogo,584379,603847,photo,3,1,0,4,"['DATE', 'ORG', 'PERSON']",0,132,5303,1,0,4,lane jeswani crossbody easily nomad likeminded backpack origami development bento lifechanging mental kish focus cult seek selfcare among health vanessa tote internationalwomensday personal transform husband carryon cofounder really lane everyday jeswani international self nomad womens development mental focus seek health vanessa personal cofounder
Indiegogo,584379,603847,video,6,3,0,549,['ORG'],0,132,5303,0,1,7,lead studio telescopic remote mini imaging sirui transform tube remote transform studio
GoFundMe,1820041,1922428,video,382,314,155,21178,"['NORP', 'CARDINAL', 'PERSON', 'GPE', 'MONEY']",0,133,4545,215,3,600,mila standwithukraine already 30 official donor refugee deliver relief nonprofit 20 ukrainian mila ukraine 20
Indiegogo,584397,603864,photo,0,1,0,1,['ORG'],0,133,5303,0,1,1,brand indiegogos potential teaming acquisition accelerate icymi enable platform brand
Kickstarter,1594105,1591749,link,10,6,0,14,"['QUANTITY', 'PRODUCT']",0,133,4839,4,0,14,accuracy aim scanner compromise 3d lizard detail view capture scanner 3d 3d match exclusive printer diy model perfect printing accuracy mm affordable
Indiegogo,584397,603864,video,3,1,0,387,['ORG'],0,133,5303,0,3,6,brand news indiegogos potential consumer accelerate acquisition enable platform brand growth ecommerce consumer accelerate
Indiegogo,584397,603864,photo,1,1,0,3,"['ORG', 'PRODUCT', 'CARDINAL', 'TIME', 'DATE', 'MONEY']",0,133,5303,0,2,3,sign draft page cornerstone worth chance linkedin win pst1 attend strategy entire pm select innovator prize webinar 35 ready 50 plus spot effective est successful zoom page 23rd 130 champion ampst engagement pm 2022 march webinar pmest 1030 effective wednesday zoom
Indiegogo,584397,603864,video,7,3,1,1103,['PERSON'],0,133,5303,5,2,14,else ride fun escooter serious else ride fun escooter serious
Kickstarter,1594142,1591775,link,10,6,0,10,"['LANGUAGE', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'PERSON']",0,134,4839,0,0,10,sensitive korean alison nt situation explain suck die attack
Indiegogo,584408,603878,video,4,3,1,664,"['CARDINAL', 'DATE', 'PERSON']",0,134,5303,0,2,6,purrini fourlegged ton configuration modular custom cat diy anything kitty playground tree caturday castle custom playground kitty diy
Indiegogo,584408,603878,video,1,3,0,475,['ORG'],0,134,5303,0,3,4,builtin gaming haptic entertainment action screen goto happen chair motion vibe chair actually goto builtin haptic
Kickstarter,1594142,1591775,photo,6,3,0,6,['DATE'],0,134,4839,0,0,6,playful ambitious throughout march creatively subversive brilliant
Indiegogo,584409,603870,video,5,4,0,860,"['ORG', 'NORP', 'PRODUCT', 'EVENT', 'PERSON']",0,135,5303,1,1,7,rgb instant lightning content films studio reviews effect telescopic remote french mini rolling julia cute unboxes swell led internationalwomensday sirui tube rgb telescopic roll mini led tube
Indiegogo,584409,603870,photo,2,1,1,3,"['ORG', 'NORP', 'PERSON', 'DATE', 'GPE']",0,135,5303,1,0,3,guide africa comfortable tour mpii asset publish agency aka afro cafe spot develop intuition la beyond elevate shrink authentic walking internationalwomensday ceo paris jacqueline african ngo hotel dedicate spends commercial event everyday jacqueline international womens africa ngo comfortable shrink authentic mpii ceo develop intuition asset paris
Indiegogo,584409,603870,video,0,1,0,5530,"['EVENT', 'DATE', 'ORG', 'PRODUCT']",0,135,5303,0,0,0,celebration beyond labs monthlong roundtable wuuk matebike 2022 thekeepers internationalwomensday womenled conversation doorbell wuuk hang matebike doorbell thekeepers lets labs
Kickstarter,1594178,1591805,link,15,2,0,20,[],0,135,4839,5,0,20,bar pint sport hub aim womens burger bar bra restaurant womens sports culture empower cheer promote drink sport eat
Indiegogo,584409,603870,video,2,1,1,320,"['EVENT', 'DATE', 'ORG']",0,135,5303,0,1,3,everyday international primarily commit particularly occasion womens beyond venture us folk real 2020 white hard seriously reality funding important thrive throughout innovator internationalwomensday capital womenled acknowledge ongoing everyday international womens
Indiegogo,584409,603870,video,2,2,0,234,"['CARDINAL', 'ORG']",0,135,5303,0,0,2,target podcast listen headphone apple subscribe episode official audience strategy reveal drop campaigner podcatcher allnew choice practice advertising podcast episode 14 episodego drop
Indiegogo,584409,603870,video,6,1,3,701,['ORG'],0,136,5303,0,1,7,pretty question wild comment typically size motor upcoming twice munity anything prelaunch drop eins plus conversation eins
Kickstarter,1594233,1591848,link,10,1,1,12,['ORG'],0,136,4839,2,0,12,output content youtube hq expand league la expansion dirt level
Indiegogo,584424,603875,video,3,4,1,856,['ORG'],0,136,5303,0,0,3,buzz ust 4k comfort movie projector vision comfort movie
Indiegogo,584424,603875,link,2,4,0,4,"['CARDINAL', 'DATE', 'ORG']",0,136,5303,0,0,2,season corner hi spring invention 2022 february handheld else gaming february
Kickstarter,1594233,1591848,link,8,3,1,9,"['PERSON', 'ORG', 'PRODUCT']",0,136,4839,1,0,9,radical force reveal imagination core revolutionary rover reimagine mars
Indiegogo,584424,603875,video,2,3,3,612,"['ORDINAL', 'ORG', 'PRODUCT']",0,136,5303,1,0,3,enter ayaneo ryzen handheld trigger gaming sensor ultimate hall amd 7 joystick aaa windows handheld gaming gamer
Indiegogo,584424,603875,video,3,2,2,358,['ORG'],0,136,5303,2,0,5,question hot got comment coffee beverage temperature perfect upcoming tea munity prelaunch drop lid conversation
Indiegogo,584424,603875,video,3,3,0,247,"['CARDINAL', 'ORG']",0,139,5303,0,0,3,podcast conversion listen deadline headphone close apple subscribe episode official optimize postcampaign increase trick strategy drop campaigner podcatcher allnew choice sense option podcast episode 13 episodego drop
Kickstarter,1594374,1591975,video,21,5,3,27,"['CARDINAL', 'PERSON']",0,139,4839,3,3,27,huge four brandon secret congratulation novel wow
Indiegogo,584497,603911,photo,33,9,6,40,"['GPE', 'PERSON']",0,140,5303,6,1,40,standwithukraine resource link bio solidarity ukraine blog war ongoing e ukraine
Indiegogo,584497,603911,photo,50,36,3,66,"['GPE', 'PERSON']",0,140,5303,14,2,66,solidarity war standwithukraine ukraine ongoing e ukraine
Kickstarter,1594379,1591982,link,16,8,1,22,"['ORG', 'CARDINAL', 'PERSON', 'DATE', 'GPE']",0,140,4839,6,0,22,cinema front satellite result states swamp audience united rifftrax beam return rifftrax 2022 swamp return august 600 theater nashville rifftrax 2022 movie nationwide 18 swamp return
Kickstarter,1594397,1592002,link,7,4,0,7,"['CARDINAL', 'GPE']",0,141,4839,0,0,7,shop wants chance souvenir york memory hold souvenir apple shop item souvenir print feat jewelry tshirt shoe apple
Kickstarter,1594397,1592002,link,28,3,1,29,"['CARDINAL', 'DATE', 'ORG', 'PERSON']",0,141,4839,1,0,29,prolific print four brandon books sanderson fantasy choice format author audiobook surprise brandon sanderson four novel secret swag box enjoy throughout 2023 sanderson
GoFundMe,1817687,1919899,photo,94,319,40,319,"['ORG', 'CARDINAL', 'ORDINAL', 'GPE', 'MONEY']",0,142,4545,20,9,123,humanitarian already round securely us central update immediate safely ground ukraine relief nonprofit grant children kitchen humanitarian donation ukraine
Indiegogo,584502,603889,photo,2,5,0,5,"['ORG', 'NORP', 'PERSON', 'DATE', 'ORDINAL']",0,142,5303,0,0,2,innovation everyday blackhistorymonth ntribution daily discovery african highlight womens scientific recognize past generation groundbreaking reality american forward throughout mark holidays february instagramcomindiegogo improve invention pave crowdfunde inventor ann wait lead earn dr experiment jackson mit cable invention indiegogos
Kickstarter,1594451,1592056,link,12,5,0,12,"['ORG', 'PRODUCT']",0,142,4839,0,0,12,grip switch equip oled case nintendo bluetooth battery interchangeable switch oled case allinone gaming nintendo modular grip low extra case slot detachable card battery interchangeable
Kickstarter,1594486,1592089,link,14,2,0,20,['PERSON'],0,143,4839,6,0,20,spirit empower children lift aim representation dear brown journey discover empower children inspiring shine within
Kickstarter,1594486,1592089,link,19,9,3,21,['ORDINAL'],0,143,4839,2,0,21,physically bare content virtual connection reality human bare emerge vr physically
GoFundMe,1817884,1920077,link,77,342,41,342,"['ORG', 'DATE', 'GPE']",0,146,4545,26,6,109,affect safety add response current individual centralized hub verify ukraine verified crisis trust ukraine effort commit ukraine relief
Kickstarter,1594619,1592209,link,24,4,2,26,"['DATE', 'PERSON']",0,146,4839,2,0,26,handheld literature gothic modern player horror handheld ode era modern
Indiegogo,584544,603887,link,5,8,1,8,"['DATE', 'ORG', 'ORDINAL']",0,147,5303,0,2,7,packable kayak content exciting exclusive gadget rpg tabletop invention crowdfunde 2022 march packable promise maker ice kayak exciting cream 2022 march tabletop
Kickstarter,1594677,1592268,link,6,4,0,6,"['CARDINAL', 'DATE', 'GPE']",0,147,4839,0,0,6,reflection animate girls adapt wake mississippi horror ride anyone miss
Indiegogo,584551,603882,video,9,12,1,1141,['ORG'],0,148,5303,2,1,12,severe condition waterproof weather wherever outdoor station invent waterproof outdoor station
Indiegogo,584551,603882,video,5,5,12,1082,[],0,148,5303,4,4,13,hive invent bee answer protection adjustable bee answer protection
Kickstarter,1594729,1592323,link,19,3,2,20,['CARDINAL'],0,148,4839,1,0,20,mic serve equip bluetooth recorder touch mighty standard midi contact wifi tutor surface recorder controller coach tutor midi audio guitar app interact progress performance track ukulele record
Indiegogo,584575,603894,photo,3,7,0,7,"['ORG', 'CARDINAL', 'TIME', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'DATE']",0,149,5303,1,0,4,sign chance linkedin hey case pst1 223 strategy engagement tomorrow pm webinar campaigner study est zoom feb 23rd 130 linkedin champion ampst engagement pm accelerate 2022 1000 webinar growth 1030 wednesday
Indiegogo,584575,603894,video,3,4,1,346,"['CARDINAL', 'ORG', 'PRODUCT']",0,149,5303,0,1,4,advice podcast stretch expert algorithm listen headphone momentum apple subscribe visibility episode contest official reveal digital drop campaigner podcatcher allnew choice tactic achieve secret podcast episode 12 episodego drop
Indiegogo,584575,603894,video,10,2,0,1292,"['CARDINAL', 'ORG', 'PRODUCT']",0,149,5303,2,0,12,gimbal question 3axis got upcoming moment swiss munity army vlogging conversation 4k capture knife cam gimbal 4k
Kickstarter,1594772,1592365,link,13,7,0,13,['CARDINAL'],0,149,4839,0,0,13,machine material laser engrave location hundred cutting limitless ready laser cutter material precision area folding industrial internal hundred filtration infinite accuracy
Indiegogo,584575,603894,video,6,2,3,1077,"['ORG', 'PRODUCT', 'CARDINAL', 'TIME', 'DATE', 'ORDINAL']",1,149,5303,0,0,6,longtime hr recover line body wearable todays wait therapy fave repair red relieve irl grab stateoftheart fb naturally drop fitness number flexbeam available limited athlete wearable red therapy drop stateoftheart
GoFundMe,1816528,1918712,photo,98,334,42,334,['PERSON'],0,150,4545,36,49,183,safely zuri lets
GoFundMe,1816607,1918658,video,337,229,67,31149,['PERSON'],0,152,4545,231,5,573,loud touch barber cut jackson beyond hair noise barber tiktok viral
Indiegogo,584601,603904,photo,1,2,0,2,"['CARDINAL', 'DATE', 'ORG']",0,152,5303,0,0,1,cook gear 6 outdoor invention indiegogos
Indiegogo,584601,603904,link,3,1,2,3,"['CARDINAL', 'DATE']",0,152,5303,0,0,3,6 outdoors goexplore land essential cooking gear camping gear cooking chef channel inner nature rugged guru gear
Indiegogo,584621,603912,photo,2,1,0,3,[],0,153,5303,0,1,3,endings remotely firewall exciting joy true ig router wordand fulfil firewalla shoutout beginnings ship campaigner successfully kudo perk unbox purple
Kickstarter,1594930,1592507,link,17,7,0,19,"['ORDINAL', 'NORP', 'PERSON']",0,153,4839,2,0,19,production hd format company release original anime bluray bluray 15th anniversary encourage hd unique format development release original anime bluray
Indiegogo,584621,603912,video,9,3,3,1166,['ORG'],0,153,5303,1,1,11,battery move rotate weighted require automatic co weighted require battery automatic
GoFundMe,1816313,1918469,photo,80,203,11,203,"['QUANTITY', 'DATE', 'GPE', 'PERSON']",0,154,4545,21,16,117,maine vet florida missing cat ago confused ashe denise mi 7 reunite 1500 kitten forever al maine beneficiary settle possible continue please forward ashe 2022 denise et february grateful baby
Kickstarter,1594975,1592547,link,3,1,1,3,['PERSON'],0,154,4839,0,0,3,handle distribution sharp advice budget musician printer organizer daniel interdisciplinary planning photobook handle distribution advice budget photobook printer
Indiegogo,584629,603916,video,3,5,7,983,['WORK_OF_ART'],0,154,5303,2,1,6,medieval knight happen movie fantasy indie horror medieval knight happen movie fantasy horror
Indiegogo,584652,603929,video,22,6,3,854,[],0,155,5303,2,1,25,waste button compost earthhour push
Indiegogo,584652,603929,photo,4,4,2,4,"['ORG', 'NORP', 'PRODUCT', 'PERSON', 'DATE', 'ORDINAL']",0,155,5303,0,0,4,innovation daily career shape us brandnew generation rely market step stem improve pioneer interested inventor everyday blackhistorymonth advice explorer scientific got found 1980 development groundbreaking industry modern legacy company jerry highlight avenue rom fairchild gaming reality especially channel award ground crowd invention software stop cover programmable discovery numerous african lead recognize elses atari instagram platform american forward throughout thrive february approach f instagramcomindiegogo pave adopt console f fairchild pioneer jerry modern gaming console inventor indiegogos
Kickstarter,1594992,1592565,link,4,1,0,5,"['CARDINAL', 'PERCENT']",0,155,4839,1,0,5,candle custom scent match make100 color crystal candle custom scent natural color option
Indiegogo,584652,603929,video,1,1,1,492,['ORG'],0,156,5303,0,1,2,runaway breakfast creek question inside yazebas group upcoming bed munity rpg possum tabletop conversation center magical breakfast tabletop creek rpg games possum bed yazebas
Indiegogo,584655,603923,video,0,3,0,309,"['CARDINAL', 'ORG']",0,156,5303,0,1,1,podcast conversion refund listen rate headphone leverage apple subscribe value episode official optimize strategy order reveal funding diving traffic drop campaigner podcatcher allnew choice average podcast episode drop episodego 11
Kickstarter,1595014,1592582,link,27,5,2,31,['PRODUCT'],0,156,4839,4,0,31,cinema equip allterrain surface electric cinema rover electric movement object control speed tracking precise
Indiegogo,584655,603923,video,5,1,3,1270,"['ORG', 'PRODUCT', 'CARDINAL', 'TIME', 'DATE', 'ORDINAL']",1,156,5303,3,1,9,longtime hr move line 48 todays wait fave link believe edition grab terrain bio splach fb blue drop number available escooter limited edition allterrain escooter drop limited
Indiegogo,584665,603927,photo,2,4,0,4,"['ORG', 'PRODUCT', 'CARDINAL', 'PERSON', 'TIME', 'MONEY']",1,157,5303,0,1,3,pst recover body wearable therapy repair red relieve date lets gooooo stateoftheart unit naturally drop 50 flexbeam 7 perk available notify flexbeam drop
Kickstarter,1595073,1592638,link,3,1,0,3,"['CARDINAL', 'GPE']",0,157,4839,0,0,3,shop wants chance souvenir york memory make100 hold souvenir apple shop item souvenir print feat jewelry tshirt shoe apple
Kickstarter,1595073,1592638,link,10,4,1,12,['PERSON'],0,157,4839,2,0,12,poet gerald justice scifi coleman author poem l collection poem side poetry justice collection
Indiegogo,584688,603947,video,6,4,0,732,"['WORK_OF_ART', 'CARDINAL', 'ORG', 'PERSON']",0,159,5303,0,2,8,anniversary brandon nyt edition white sanderson epic bestselling deluxe graphic dynamite sand omnibus author novel brandon sanderson deluxe nyt edition bestselling white sand author anniversary
Kickstarter,1595252,1592823,link,10,1,0,13,"['GPE', 'PERSON']",0,161,4839,3,0,13,fact state comic united pen author plan chronicle publish state united fact state comic united chronicle
Indiegogo,584712,603956,link,3,6,0,6,"['ORDINAL', 'ORG', 'PERSON']",0,161,5303,0,0,3,concept contribute exclusive holt sketch indiegogos sit platform site chat clear trustproven someone really badge trustproven reliable campaigner canon among nod platform
Indiegogo,584712,603956,link,0,3,0,3,['ORG'],0,161,5303,0,0,0,introduce initiative empower proud informed multiple fulfil effort decision campaigner spotlight manage blog trustproven foundation perk trust introduce trustproven informed introduce empower effort priority foundation decision trust proud
Kickstarter,1595252,1592823,link,13,7,0,16,"['CARDINAL', 'ORG']",0,161,4839,3,0,16,oldschool homemade make100 toaster bamboo toaster unique beautifully functional toaster beautiful bamboo
Indiegogo,584709,603950,link,3,2,0,4,"['CARDINAL', 'DATE', 'QUANTITY']",0,162,5303,1,0,4,30 handheld gaming weigh electric commuter carbon lb pc fiber january 2022 outside january 2022 clean fun
Kickstarter,1595257,1592834,link,8,17,1,17,"['DATE', 'GPE']",0,162,4839,8,1,17,complexity miami drag insight intimate todays drag scene
Indiegogo,584709,603950,photo,3,0,3,4,"['TIME', 'CARDINAL', 'ORG', 'MONEY']",1,163,5303,0,1,4,pst discount normally date lets gooooo splach unit drop 20 7 perk available notify splach plus drop
Indiegogo,584724,603957,link,2,2,0,2,"['DATE', 'ORG', 'PERSON']",0,163,5303,0,0,2,crowdfunde 2022 icymi initiative 2021 promise initiative exciting 2021 hit deliver campaigner number aim
Kickstarter,1595293,1592867,link,9,2,0,10,"['DATE', 'PERSON']",0,163,4839,1,0,10,dad sixyearold chase dreamer whose dad dad children importance highlight
Indiegogo,584724,603957,video,2,1,0,384,"['CARDINAL', 'DATE', 'ORG']",0,163,5303,0,0,2,brand crucial podcast host expert listen headphone page season apple subscribe episode days official strategy success engagement point outreach drop campaigner podcatcher allnew choice cover podcast episode episodego drop season
Indiegogo,584724,603957,photo,3,0,0,3,"['ORG', 'NORP', 'PRODUCT', 'CARDINAL', 'PERSON', 'DATE']",0,163,5303,0,0,3,innovation everyday blackhistorymonth daily morgan discovery whose african highlight scientific garrett recognize signal generation groundbreaking arrive american drive throughout traffic february improve invention pave patent modern inventor position garrett mask morgan gas traffic smoke leader inventor indiegogos
Kickstarter,1595293,1592867,link,8,1,0,8,[],0,163,4839,0,0,8,magazine literary original comic_strip globe publish comics magazine literary original stories
Kickstarter,1595329,1592903,link,5,3,1,5,['ORG'],0,164,4839,0,0,5,media furniture cooperative working print version grief faith compilation shopping mystery brick quarterly apparent brick press freedom library protect
Indiegogo,584720,603947,video,20,4,5,1475,['ORG'],0,164,5303,0,1,21,easily robotic modular arm reality diy laser robot invent quickly ai utilize 3d modular laser quickly ai arm utilize robot easily robotic 3d
Indiegogo,584720,603947,video,5,1,0,594,"['WORK_OF_ART', 'CARDINAL', 'ORG', 'PERSON']",0,164,5303,0,0,5,anniversary brandon nyt edition white sanderson epic bestselling deluxe graphic dynamite sand omnibus author novel brandon sanderson deluxe nyt edition bestselling white sand author anniversary
Indiegogo,584720,603947,photo,4,0,0,4,"['TIME', 'DATE', 'ORG']",0,164,5303,0,0,4,engaged sign track result advocate linkedin case pst1 223 strategy engagement excited effectively pm accelerate webinar campaigner growth study est successful zoom feb 23rd 130 linkedin champion ampst engagement pm accelerate 2022 1000 webinar growth 1030 pest wednesday
Kickstarter,1595329,1592903,link,5,1,0,5,[],0,164,4839,0,0,5,spirit tool communicate card divination realm tool dead magic trick bizarre word divination spirit enter tool dead trick mind card magic bizarre divination
Indiegogo,584727,603917,video,6,1,1,1134,['PRODUCT'],0,167,5303,2,1,9,remotely grid station remotely grid station
Indiegogo,584708,603878,video,7,4,2,775,"['QUANTITY', 'ORG']",0,167,5303,0,0,7,storage data tool sharing tb multiple problem waterproof datum 2200 pocketsize speed solution storage data problem solution
Kickstarter,1595467,1593035,link,11,2,0,11,['ORG'],0,167,4839,0,0,11,gap historically bridge aim college con hbcu 2022 con hbcu gap bridge
Indiegogo,584708,603878,photo,7,0,1,8,"['EVENT', 'DATE', 'ORG', 'PERSON']",0,167,5303,1,0,8,innovation celebration particularly diverse vp courage fortune pursuit resilient wish fearless global lunar strategy resilience represent luck strength lunar
Kickstarter,1595467,1593035,link,10,1,0,10,"['WORK_OF_ART', 'CARDINAL', 'PERSON']",0,167,4839,0,0,10,different wants ink watercolor make100 anthony dragon surreal landscape detailed edition dragon print limited painting different type custom select dragon commission option
Indiegogo,584712,603868,video,11,6,4,1498,['ORG'],0,168,5303,1,0,12,moment intelligent canon photography develop auto content capture tracking creation photography content creation
Indiegogo,584712,603868,video,5,2,1,940,['ORG'],0,168,5303,1,1,7,choice healthy body fat measure lifestyle fitness manage choice healthy lifestyle fitness manage
